^ ^
嘿 如果你一大早要起床趕車...
Hey, hey. If you're coming in for the morning grind...
那麼這絕對又是一個交通繁忙 惱人的週一
it's another brutal Monday out there traffic-wise.
二號道以及五號道交通繁忙
The 2 is slow-and-go to the 5.
十號道因擁堵接近癱瘓
A Sig Alert is bogging down the I-10.
如果你還在四零五高速路上
And if you're on the 405 freeway,
你上班可能就要遲到了
you're probably already late for work.
如果你的老闆要給你點顏色看看
If your boss gives you a hard time about it,
你讓他到這裡來和...
have him come down here and talk to...
- ...Rachel談談 - 噢 不
- ...Rachel. - Oh, no.
好 哈哈 謝謝 還是免了吧
Zing! Ha, ha. Thanks, Skip.
但是 說到老闆 廣告之後...
But, hey, speaking of bosses, after the break...
我們請來了三位自已創業的小伙子
we get to meet three guys
白手起家 追尋他們的夢想
who are chasing their dream of becoming their own bosses.
馬上回來
Stay with us.
暫停 很好 各位 九十秒後繼續
And we're out. Very good, guys. We're back in 90 seconds.
老闆不是人2
天啊 黛爾 你別再冒汗了
Jesus Christ. Dale, you gotta stop sweating, pal.
噢 哇 你都濕了
Oh, wow, you are wet. "Stop sweating."
"別出汗了" 怎麼讓它停下來了
How do I stop sweating?
這可是件大事 我們把全部都押在這上面了
This is a big deal. We got everything riding on this.
我們辭掉工作
We've quit our jobs,
我還有三個孩子嗷嗷待哺 怎麼說?
I have three children to think about now. How about that?
想像一下 你等下表現得亮瞎全場
Think about this. You do a good job right now,
你的兒子們絕對會以你為豪的
you're gonna make your boys very proud.
女兒 我有三個女兒 老兄
Girls. I have three girls, dude.
好吧 她們那年齡也認不出男的女的
Right. You can't even tell at that age.
她們都活像長手腳的馬鈴薯
They basically look like potatoes with arms.
別把我孩子叫作馬鈴薯
Don't call my kids potatoes.
- 尊重一下孩子們 - 別把他惹惱了
- Respect the kids. - Don't piss him off.
她們可穿得粉紅粉紅的!
They wear pink!
讓他冷靜下來
Calm him down.
很多人都喜歡穿粉色衣服
A lot of guys wear pink.
我就很喜歡我那件粉色的馬球衫
I have a pink polo shirt that I love.
快別說了
Come on.
能拿一卷紙巾過來嗎?
Can we get a roll of paper towels?
快來人拿捲紙巾!
Can I get paper towels?!
你為什麼要大吼大叫?
Why are you barking at people?
他可是禮貌地說 你卻在大吼
He's saying please, you're just barking.
- 沒禮沒貌 - 兄弟 你該把臉擦乾
- Bad manners. - Buddy, dry your face.
- 他緊張得要死 - 難以置信
- He's freaking out. - It's unbelievable.
你們沒我也行吧?
Can you go on without me?
不然你待在車裡等著?
Why don't you wait in the car?
別鬧 很簡單的 只要你放輕鬆
Stop, this is gonna be easy. You have to calm down.
聽著 尼克會用事實和數據說話
Look, Nick's gonna hit them with facts and figures,
他很有頭腦的 好不?
because he's the brains, right?
你就說說 你和你老婆怎麼天雷勾動地火
You talk about how you and your wife fucked
養大那三個馬鈴薯大的孩子
and made three potatoes with arms.
你去感化人心 我就做我該做的事 隨機應變
You're the heart. Me, I'll do my thing, get in where I fit in.
- 你是靈魂? - 不 勞資是你們的大屌
- You're the soul? - No, I'm the dick and balls.
- 明白了 - 我為什麼要當靈魂?
- Got it. - Why would I wanna be the soul?
就是別嚇昏過去 大力吸氣
Just don't pass out. Just keep breathing.
看吧 很簡單的
See? This will be easy.
我們要做的就是展現自我
All we have to do is be ourselves.
還是別展現自我了
Let's not be ourselves.
我們的自我都丟垃圾堆去了
Ourselves is a Dumpster fire.
要比自我做的更好才行 升華自我
Let's be better than ourselves. Let's try to elevate a little.
說得很好 沒人做的了自我
That's a good note. Nobody be themselves.
注意 還有二十秒節目開始
All right, we're back in 20 seconds.
嘿 小伙子們 感謝你們的到來
Hey, fellas, thanks for coming.
- 很高興見到你們 - 早安 你好嗎?
- Nice to meet you. - Good morning. How are you?
嘿 伙伴 一團糟對不
Hey, my man. There's trouble.
- 太過火了 - 他都不介意
- Too much. - Well, he went with it.
黛爾·阿爾比
Dale Arbus.
很高興認識你 伙伴
Pleasure to meet you, man.
感謝你們的到來 這肯定很有趣
Thanks for coming on. This will be fun.
是的
Yeah.
拉鏈一直都拉得這麼低嗎?
Does that zip all the way down?
離節目開始還有五 四...
And we're back in five, four...
"洛杉磯 早安"
歡迎回來 知道嗎
And we're back. You know,
我們每週都會在 "創意焦點" 中...
every week we like to highlight...
採訪本土的發明家或是企業家
local inventors and entrepreneurs in our Big Idea Spotlight.
說得對 麥克
That's right, Mike.
今天我們有幸請到三位現代安迪生...
And today we have three modern-day...
他們發明了一種新型洗浴器 並且希望它大賣
Edisons who've created a new shower gadget they hope to really clean up with.
有請尼克·庫爾特還有黛爾
Please, welcome Nick, Kurt and Dale.
很高興來到現場
Pleasure to be here.
在我們介紹你們的產品之前
Before we get to the product,
能告訴我們...
can you tell us...
是什麼激發了
what is it that
你們三個人自己去創業的想法呢?
inspired three regular Joes to go into business for yourselves?
我們三個都曾為討人厭的上司倍受屈辱地工作
We were all working at pretty terrible jobs for some awful bosses.
然後就想 如果我們自己當老闆
And thought if we got a chance to be our own bosses,
我們肯定不會像他們一樣
we'd do things differently.
這就是我們的機遇
This might be our shot.
我們從未想過有這機會
We didn't think we'd get the chance,
但是黛爾有個很棒的想法
but Dale had an amazing idea.
別讓黛爾搭話
Don't go to Dale.
後來 我們就開始聚在一起 討論發明...
And, we started meeting together to talk about the invention...
不再抱怨鬧心的工作
instead of complaining about our jobs.
嘿 我覺得這真是讓人 "性" 奮
Hey, I think that's exciting.
黛爾 我想問
Dale, you know, I just wanna know,
是什麼激發你的靈感...
where did the idea come from...
...去設計一個新型蓮蓬頭?
...for a new showerhead?
我有三個孩子
I have three kids.
我是來談心的
So that's the heart.
- 真是幸福 - 是的 他有三胞胎
- That's a blessing. - Yeah, well, he has triplets.
說實話 有點多了 鴨梨山大
In all honesty, it's too many. I'm pretty overwhelmed.
很顯然 他心思全在那上面了
Well, he's got them on his mind, clearly.
我來回答吧
Let me answer the question.
黛爾當時從一個自助洗車服務回來...
Dale, had just gotten back from one of those self-service car washes...
... 那裡有杆 有肥皂
...with the wand with the soap.
總之是所有東西的結合體
It's got everything in one thing.
他就想 "為什麼不給我們
He thought, "Why don't they make one of
設計一個類似的東西呢"
these for your body?"
在我們幾杯酒下肚之後 靈光一閃
After we had a few beers, we came up with the,
就想出 "洗浴好基友" 了
Shower Buddy.
"洗浴好基友"?
The Shower Buddy?
不好意思 那名字還只是暫定而已
I'm sorry, that name's not official yet.
不 他說錯了 是正式的
No, he's wrong. It is official.
我想取名為 "洗浴好爹地"
I wanted the "Shower Daddy."
"洗浴好爹地" 這名字真是爛出新高度
"Shower Daddy" is worse on every level.
我同意尼克說的
I have to agree with Nick.
好過有個怪咖和你一起洗澡
Better than having some strange dude with you.
才不是怪咖呢 老兄
It's not some strange dude, Dale,
我說過多少次了 是你的好基友
as I've said many times. It's your buddy.
為什麼讓你的好基友和你一起洗澡?
Why would your buddy be in the shower?
為什麼要和你爸爸?
Why would your dad?
別在節目上大吼大叫
Don't scream on television.
不如這樣
You know what?
小伙子們 向我們展示展示你們的小發明吧
How about you fellas show us how this gizmo works?
好吧? 咱們走吧
Right? Let's get it going.
好 看看吧 拿出來秀秀
Yes. Make it rain. Yes. Work it, work it.
噢 真是帥呆了
Oh, this is awesome.
庫爾特會進去 打開水龍頭
So Kurt's gonna go ahead and get in there. He's gonna turn on the shower.
你們就會看到水流出來
You're gonna see the water come out.
過一會 洗髮液就會自動從蓮蓬頭噴出來
After a bit, the shampoo's gonna automatically be triggered out of the showerhead...
- 沒有水壓 - 那個藍色把手
- No water pressure. - The blue handle.
- 沒有水壓 - 後面有一個抽水機
- No water pressure. - There's a pump on the back.
我可以手動抽水
I could pump it manually.
黛爾去幫幫忙 謝謝你 老兄
Dale's gonna help out. Thank you, buddy.
- 抽水機 - 你搞得定嗎?
- Pump. - You got it?
- 可以的 - 好
- I got it. - Yeah?
水流出來後 洗髮液就會順著水流出來...
Water comes out, the shampoo mixes with the water...
緊接著 就會流出護髮液
then shortly after that, conditioner.
所以用 "洗浴好基友"
You shower in half the time
只花你平時一半的時間
with the Shower Buddy.
大多數美國人... 不知道你聽說過沒...
The average American... I don't know if you know this....
平均每週工作五十多小時
spends 50 hours a week working.
- 手酸死了 - 來 我幫你
- Hand's cramping up. - Here, let me help.
... 如果我們能替你們剩下五分鐘...
...commuting. If we can save you just five minutes...
- 杆子是太乾燥了嗎? - 對 吐點口水潤滑
- The whole rod's too dry, right? - Yeah, spit on it.
- 好點沒? - 看吧 加了潤滑劑好點吧
- Better? - See, yeah. If you lube it up, it's better.
沒錯 確實是
Oh, no, absolutely.
抱歉 這機器背後有個洞 我得用手指戳一下
I'm sorry. There's a hole in the back. I'm gonna stick my finger in it.
我們不想知道你怎麼搞定的
We don't really care how you get it done.
趕快弄好它 儘快結束
Just get it done. Get it finished.
- 無論如何搞定它 - 直播嘛 對吧?
- Whatever it takes. - Live TV, right?
現場直播 你能怎麼辦?
Live TV. What are you gonna do?
- 好了 有水了 - 終於射出來了
- Yeah. Here we go. - Oh, here it comes.
嘿
Hey!
- 我早就說過 - 就像預先想的一樣好使 對吧
- I told you. - Works just as promised, okay?
- 好了 現在可以關了 - 太炫酷了 我想要一個
- Now, go ahead and shut it off. - It's so cool. I want one.
你不能帶走這一個 這是原型機
You can't have this one. It's the prototype.
但我們在找投資商
But we're looking for partners.
我說句話吧 我想加入 我來投資
I'll tell you right now. I'm sold. I wanna invest.
終於找到一個了 麥克
We got one. All right, Mike.
怎麼和你們聯繫呢?
Now, how would I get in touch with you guys?
- 你可以上我們的網站- 抱歉 沒聽清
- You go straight to Nickkurtdale. - I'm sorry, what?
我們的網站 尼克kurtdale.com
It's our website. Nickkurtdale. com.
我確定我還是沒把名字聽清楚
I'm positive I'm not hearing that right.
是我們的名字 尼克·庫爾特·黛爾
It's our names: Nick, Kurt, Dale.
尼克庫爾特黛爾
Nickkurtdale.
快換掉那名字吧
Y'all gotta change that name.
不敢相信我們之前沒有像這樣宣傳
Cannot believe we never said it out loud before.
紙上寫的挺好的啊
It looked so good on paper.
可惜只是黃粱美夢
It was a nice dream while it lasted,
還是想想怎麼求回我們以前的工作吧
but I think it's time we all go beg for our jobs back.
也許改接受現實了 我們根本不是造機器的料
Maybe just accept the fact that we'll always be cogs in the machine.
等等 "造機器的屌" 那是什麼?
Wait. Cocks in the machine. What is that?
是 "料" 開頭的
"Cogs." Guh.
知道嗎? 你說得對 我們不是當老闆的料
You know what? You're right. We're not boss material.
我們像工蜂一樣 像豬一樣賣力幹
We're worker bees. We're grunts.
噢 老兄 那首歌 我現在聽不得
Oh, boy. That song. I can't hear that now.
調成振動吧
Just put it on vibrate.
你能消停點嗎?
Will you stop? Please?
我專門調這歌激勵我們的
I picked this song to inspire us.
至少不是激勵我
It's not inspiring me.
快看 未知來電
Look at this. Unknown caller.
- 趕緊接了吧 - 你好?
- Just answer it. - Hello?
是 我是 "洗浴好基友" 的
Yup, this is one of the Shower Buddy guys.
真的? 是的 不 當然 我當然知道你是誰
Really? Yes. No, of course. I know exactly who you are.
查查 "比爾德·斯特姆" 是什麼鬼
Look up "Boulder Stream." Boulder Stream.
謝謝 我們以我們的產品為豪
Thank you. We're very proud of the product.
是 如果能用郵件把詳情發給我們 就再好不過了
Yeah, if you just e-mail us the details, that'll be fine.
不是在做夢吧?
Is that a real thing?
- 嗯 我的信箱? - 別用你的
- Yeah, my e-mail? - Not yours.
嗯 是phatballllz@hotmail.com
Yeah, it's phatballllz@hotmail.com.
是P-H-A-T-B-A-L-L...
It's P-H-A-T-B-A-L-L...
L-L-Z...
@hotmail.com
@hotmail.com.
好 謝謝你
Yeah. All right. Thank you. Yeah.
- 明天見 - 哇
- See you tomorrow. - Wow.
臥勒個槽 比爾德·斯特姆對 "洗浴好基友" 感興趣
Holy shit. Boulder Stream loves the Shower Buddy.
比爾德·斯特姆到底是什麼鬼?
Who the fuck is Boulder Stream?
北美首屈一指 最大的零售商
Only one of the largest catalog retailers in North America.
真不錯
Nice.
當你心情好時 聽起來就很不錯
When you're in a good mood, it's a good song.
心情不好 就覺得很爛
Bad mood, bad song.
這就是藝術 真是良曲
That's art. That's good art.
- 老兄 這地方真是豪氣 - 是 很不錯
- Man, this place is legit. - Yeah, it's nice.
你看到那些免費餅乾嗎?
Did you see the free cookies?
你肯定看到了 你都快吃了四個了
Yeah, you clearly have. That's four of those.
你會吃得滿臉都是巧克力的
You're gonna have chocolate on your face.
當我們見到這個人時...
When we meet this guy...
在握手的時候
when you shake his hand,
記得用另一隻手摸對方的肘
- 這麼握逼格很高 - 我不會握 做給我看看
- It's a classy move. - I don't know this move. Let me see.
- 像這樣 - 拜託 靜靜好嗎
- Like that. - Please, both sit down.
- 真不賴 - 這樣如何? 還不錯
- That's nice. - How about that? Not bad.
- 確實不錯 - 你手指沾滿巧克力了
- That's really good. - You got chocolate on your fingers.
現在沾到我夾克上了
Now it's on my jacket.
拿點水抹掉
Put water on it.
不要水擦 那樣會讓汙漬凝固的
I don't need water. That will set it.
別拿著餅乾離我這麼近
Get the cookie away from me.
不會 就像以毒攻毒那樣
No, it's like a fire-on-fire thing.
不 水會越弄越糟
No, the water will set it.
哈! 你們都到了 我的 "洗浴好基友"
Ha! There they are. There are my shower buddies.
你們好嗎? 活生生站在面前
How are you? In the flesh.
還以為是早間節目呢
It's just like on that morning show.
你們總是在奮鬥 我很欣賞
You're always fighting. I love it.
- 確實是...  - 我是雷斯特·漢森
- Yeah, it's a... - Rex Hanson.
- 噢 嘿 庫爾特·馬克曼- 幸會
- Oh, hey. Kurt Buckman. - Good to see you.
- 幸會 - 握得很優雅
- Nice to see you. - Classy handshake.
- 我是尼克·亨德里克斯 - 尼克 幸會
- Nick Hendricks. - Nick, pleasure.
你好 我是黛爾·阿爾布...
Hey, Dale Arb...
握住 我剛剛才學會
Shoot. I just learned it.
你想怎麼握就怎麼握
We can do it whichever way you want.
- 對吧? - 澄清一點 我們沒有種族偏見
- Right? - To be clear, we're not racist.
那很好 能幫上大忙
Well, that's good. We can use that.
伙伴們 為何不吃點點心 喝點咖啡呢?
Guys, Why don't we grab the refreshments, coffee?
拿些餅乾吧
Grab some cookies.
咱們上樓吧 談談你們的產品
Let's head upstairs. Let's talk about this product.
這是燈芯絨西裝嗎?
Is that corduroy?
進來吧 夢想終會實現
Step inside. Dreams do come true.
你們想喝點小酒嗎?
You guys want something to drink?
- 我要一杯 - 當然
- I'll take one. - Sure.
- 算了 現在還很早 - 我們就免了 抱歉
- No. It's very early. - No for us. Sorry.
我就不拐彎抹角了 先生們
I'm gonna cut right to it, gentlemen.
"洗浴好基友" 還算不錯
The Shower Buddy: a home run.
漢森先生 我們會更滿意的...
Well, Mr. Hanson, we couldn't be happier...
漢森先生是我父親 叫我雷克斯
Mr. Hanson is my father. It's "Rex."
請坐 請自便 隨便坐吧
Please, sit down. Get comfortable. Take a seat.
我想說的是 貴公司和我們合作
We want you to know that we are a company
絕對不會讓你後悔的
you can be very proud to be in business with.
我們的雇員會有健康保險 他們都會...
Our workers are all gonna have health care, they are gonna be...
我他媽一點都不關心那個
I don't really give a shit about that.
看看這個 這是吉米·亨德里克斯的吉他
Do you see this? This is Jimi Hendrix's actual guitar.
沒錯 就是著火燒著他手指頭的那一個
Yeah. The one he did the fire and fingers thing with.
喜歡這樣的酷東西嗎?
You like cool shit like this?
- 我們都愛酷東西 - 愛死了
- We love cool shit. - I'm into cool shit.
你們喜歡那種牛逼武士嗎?
You like fucking samurais?
武士? 當然了
Samurais? Sure.
知道你們喜歡 和我做生意
I knew you did. You get the business with me,
你們會有很多像這樣的牛逼收藏的
you're gonna have fucking loads of it.
所以你是提議把我們的產品...
So you are offering to carry our product...
等等 瞧瞧這個
Wait a minute. Check this out.
朗小姐 勞煩你過來一下
Miss Lang, will you come in here a moment?
現在是怎樣?
Now what?
天啊
Jesus fucking Christ.
親愛的 我們費勁腦汁
Sweetheart, we were racking our brains.
啤酒罐到底是用什麼做的?
What's a beer can made out of?
你是說鋁嗎?
Do you mean aluminum?
- 是這樣的 朗小姐 謝謝你 - 好的
- That'll be all, Miss Lang. Thank you. - Okay.
她要去哪裡?
And where does she go now?
這就是你們所嚮往的酷東西
Now, that is the kind of cool shit you have to look forward to.
這就是交易最棒的地方 你都不用親自操心
Best part about this deal: you're not gonna have to lift a finger.
本公司會承擔產品未來的發展...
My company will assume all future product development...
外包到天朝生產...
outsource manufacturing to China...
你們會一次性收到一筆 "英俊的" 報酬
and you receive a handsome one-time development fee.
我想深入談談這費用的問題...
I wanna dig in on the one-time fee because...
看到這個橄欖球了嗎?
You see this football?
是培頓·曼寧拋出後
This is the one Peyton Manning threw
那人用頭盔接住的那個 拿去吧
and the guy caught it in his helmet. Keep it.
知道嗎? 雷克斯 關於報酬的問題
You know, Rex, the one-time fee thing,
我們不太想放棄我們公司的所有權
we're not looking to give up control of the company.
是的 我們想負責生產的部分
Right. We wanna handle all the manufacturing
而貴公司負責行銷
and you guys do distribution.
什麼 你們負責生產? 在美國本土?
What, you manufacture? Here, in America?
- 計劃之中的 - 就像美國夢之類的
- That's the plan. - The American-dream thing.
小子 我不想打擊你
Boys, I hate to break it to you,
但俗話說 "美國創造 中國製造"
but the American dream, it's made in China.
聽著 很傻很天真 但我尊重你們...
Now, look, I respect your naivete...
但恐怕這筆交易只能這麼處理
but I'm afraid that this deal only happens one way.
我剛剛說了"英俊的"報酬 不是嗎?
I did say "handsome fee", right?
能給我一點時間嗎? 我想和我的合伙人談談
Can I have one minute? Just love to talk to my partners.
好吧 慢慢來 我去那邊等著
You got it. Take your time. I'll be over here.
- 噢 伙伴 - 老兄
- Oh, boy. - Man.
- 你們覺得怎麼樣? - 我不知道說什麼好...
- What do you think? - I didn't wanna say anything...
他指的可能是伊萊·曼寧 並非培頓·曼寧
but he means Eli Manning, not Peyton Manning.
可能是吧 庫爾特你呢?
Yeah. Maybe. Maybe. Kurt.
我覺得那女的身材真他媽正點
I think she has an amazing fucking body...
她的口音又讓她性感了許多
but that accent puts her over the top.
簡直不可思議 還有那條裙子
It's insane. That dress.
我同意你們倆說的 但是對那筆交易怎麼說?
Agreed on both points. How about the deal?
- 那筆交易 拿下它吧 - 我們該接受
- The deal. Gotta take it. - We should take it.
- 拿錢走人 - 他有這麼多酷東西
- Take the money and get out. - He's got cool shit.
想像一下 你也擁有這些
Imagine having your own cool shit.
但是仔細看看這裡
But look at this place.
這人靠他的公司賺了很多錢...
I mean, these guys make loads of money selling stuff...
但他覺得我們的產品還不錯
and he just called our Shower Buddy a home run.
為何要把一支潛力股就這樣賣出去呢?
Why sell a home run for a one-time fee?
很有道理
That's a good point.
我也不知道
I don't know.
我拿這錢養活史黛西 還有我的女兒們
I could use the money for Stacy and the girls.
這也有道理 真的 我也需要錢
That's a good point. That's true. I could use money.
我懂的 但這不僅僅只是錢的問題
I get that. But maybe it's not just about the money.
有道理
That's a good point.
可能還關係到 不再為任何人工作
Maybe it's about never having to work for anybody ever again.
- 說得對 - 對吧? 自己當老闆
- That's right. - Right? Being our own bosses.
- 要我說還是得指望我們自己 - 我也是
- I say we bet on ourselves. - Me too.
- 你說得對 - 我同意
- You're right. - I'm in.
我也同意 就這麼幹
I'm in. Let's do it.
好吧 雷克斯
Okay. Rex. Ahem.
- 我們拒絕你的提議 - 抱歉
- No deal. - Sorry.
- 我們還是打算自己幹 - 是嗎?
- We're, betting on ourselves. - Is that right?
對 不要難受
Yeah. And no hard feelings.
我們還是很感激你那慷慨的提議的
Honestly, we really appreciate the offer.
- 抱歉 - 我尊重你們的決定
- Sorry. - Yeah. I can respect that.
要拒絕三百萬大洋 確實需要莫大的勇氣
Takes some serious balls to walk away from 3 million bucks.
等等 三百萬美元? 我們接受了
Hang on. Three million dollars? We'll take that.
抱歉 提議收回了
Sorry. Offer's off the table.
那就一半 一半總可以了吧 一半可以嗎?
We'll take half. Half is fine. Can we have half?
過這村沒這店 總之感謝你們的到來
Ship's sailed. Thank you so much for coming in.
黛爾把那球還給我吧
Dale, I'm gonna need that ball back.
祝君在美國創業順利
Good luck building something in America.
你們要知道...
You know...
我當初在美國可是白手起家的
I built this company from the bottom up here in America.
父親 沒注意你回來了
Dad, I didn't know you were back.
我說了你能用我的辦公室嗎?
What'd I tell you about using my office?
- 我知道 我就想... 你懂的... - 我是伯特·漢森
- I know, I just thought, you know... - Bert Hanson.
你們幾個就是"浴室好基友"的合伙人嗎
You're the Shower Buddy guys?
- 是的 先生 - 對 我們就是 先生
- Yes, sir. - Yeah. We are, sir.
我對你們想要大幹一場並希望有所作為
I respect you gentlemen for wanting
而最終確立了自己地位的精神
to roll up your sleeves and build something...
表示尊敬...
stake your claim.
其實 我來到這個國家的時候一無所有
Now, I came to this country with nothing.
通過冒險以及艱辛工作
And through risk and hard work,
我的美國夢才得以實現
I made my own American dream come true.
- 你很厲害啊 - 嗯 繼續聽著
- Good for you. - Well, here's what I'm gonna do.
我會把我與太平洋沿岸國家的關係介紹給你們
I'll refer you to my contact at Pacific Shore National.
- 那是個銀行 - 他們不會不給你們貸款...
- That's a bank. - They won't balk at giving you a loan...
一旦他們聽到伯特·漢森
once they hear that Bert Hanson
剛開始就一下訂了 呃...
just has placed an initial order of, say...
十萬套
100,000 units?
- 十萬套的"浴室好基友"嗎 - 哇哦 哈
- A hundred-thousand Shower Buddies? - Whoa. Ha!
你要十萬套"浴室好基友"嗎
You're gonna make 100,000 Shower Buddies?
老爸 你在說什麼 我們可從來不做這種買賣
Dad, what are you talking about? We never make this kind of deal.
很抱歉 先生
I'm sorry, sir.
但是比爾德·斯特姆得做你們的獨家零售商
But Boulder Stream needs to be your exclusive retailer.
讓我仔細想想 可以
Let's think it over. Of course.
我們一定不會答應另外其他人的請求的
We won't pick up the phone if anyone calls.
- 就這麼定了嗎 - 必須的 就這麼定了
- We have a deal? - Yeah, you got a fucking deal.
哎 真是太好了 真棒
Hey, all right. There it is.
我抓到他的手腕了 哈
I got his elbow. Yeah.
- 我從你那裡拿了點巧克力呢 - 沒關係
- I got some chocolate on you there. - It doesn't matter.
太棒了 這真是個好消息
That's great. That is good news.
這裡有兩萬平方英尺大 但租賃期至少為五年
So it's 20,000 square feet, but it's a minimum five-year lease.
兩萬平方英尺
Twenty thousand.
聽起來比我們所需要的面積要大得多
That sounds like a lot more than we need.
但我們也需要放些東西進來 不是嗎
But we want something we can grow into, right?
我們的確有筆大單 尼克
And we have a really big order, Nick.
說得對 來吧 尼克
Damn straight. Come on, Nick.
- 尼克 叫你呢 - 我什麼也不知道
- Nick. Nick. - I don't know.
- 你明白我的意思 我是說就它吧 就是它了 - 對
- You know, I say we take it. I say we take it. - Yes.
- 對 就它了 - 太棒了
- Yes, we do. - Excellent.
你沒有一點工作經驗
You've got no work experience at all.
這很糟糕嗎
Is that bad?
開玩笑的吧 這樣很好
Are you kidding? It's great.
- 你熱情飛揚而又精力十足 - 並且不夠資格
- You're enthusiastic and you're unjaded. - And unqualified.
- 告訴你 你被僱傭了 - 哎喲
- You know what? You're hired. - Oops.
- 真的嗎 - 這真讓人出乎意料 並且 毫不值得
- Really? - That was unexpected and, undeserving.
你被僱傭了
You're hired.
通過 很明顯你通過了
That's a yes. That's an obvious yes.
- 呃 又一個... - 沒有一點工作經驗
- Well, again... - No résumé at all.
不需要那個 你的眼睛已經告訴我們一切了 你很誠實
Don't need it. Your eyes speak. You seem honest.
等下 伙伴
Hold on, pal.
- 你被僱傭了 - 真的嗎
- You're hired. - Really?
- 如果你選擇加入我們的話 - 謝謝
- I mean, if you'll have us. - Thank you.
- 越來越快了 - 呃...
- Becoming faster now. - Well...
- 你能從週六晚開始上班嗎 - 當然可以
- Can you start on Saturday evening? - Absolutely.
那太棒了 我到時候找你
Okay, great, I'll get ahold of you.
上面說的你曾經犯過重罪
Says here you've been convicted of a felony.
那都是胡說八道
That was bullshit.
雖然我明白 但我還是同意你的觀點
Word up, though, I get that, man.
就像 噗 我有過類似的經歷
Like, pfft, I had a similar thing.
他們認定我就是個兒童性犯罪者
They tried to peg me as a child sex offender.
那真是瞎扯淡
It was total bullshit.
哦 喂 喂 喂 我可不喜歡兒童性犯罪者
Oh, yo, yo, yo. I ain't down with no kid-fuckers.
我當然對兒童沒有那種意思
I'm not down with kid shit either.
嗯 我們都沒有
Yeah, none of us are.
真的沒有 伙伴
N-to-the-O, brother.
他在我們這裡不通過
We do not support that at all.
呃 我們就給他這份工作吧 我僅僅是...
But, you know, let's just give the guy a job.
呃 不想讓這個伙伴沮喪
Just... Yeah. I don't wanna upset this guy.
蒂芙尼 告訴你 你被僱傭了
Well, tell you what, Tiffany. You're hired.
- 我被僱傭了嗎 - 是啊
- I'm hired? - Yeah, you are.
- 行了 就這樣 - 哦 謝謝
- There you go. There you go. - Oh, thank you.
我們稍後週一再見 你可以離開了
We'll see you later. See you Monday. Get out of here.
庫爾特 你別僱傭惹火卻沒有經驗的女人了
Kurt, you gotta stop hiring hot unqualified women.
如果不讓美女簇擁周圍
What's the point of being boss
那麼你當老闆的意義何在呢
if you can't stock the pond?
如果沒有這些女人 你就夜不能寐嗎
You realize you can't sleep with these women?
- 你說什麼 - 作為老闆 你這是性騷擾
- What? - You're the boss. It's sexual harassment.
還記得性騷擾的事情嗎
Remember sexual harassment?
我差點殺了我老闆 還有印象嗎
I tried to kill my boss. Ring a bell?
我要把她們都解僱了嗎 我才剛僱傭了她們啊
I gotta fire them all now? We just hired them.
你不能解僱她們因為你不能和她們滾床單
You can't fire them because you're not allowed to sleep with them.
同樣因為性騷擾事件
Also sexual harassment.
我們為什麼要這樣做呢
Why are we even doing this, then?
好了 下面談一下著裝標準
All right, let's talk dress code.
- 這個無關緊要 - 這裡沒有著裝標準
- Forget it. - There is no dress code.
- 來吧 - 想怎麼穿就怎麼穿
- Come on. - You can dress however you want.
只要自己感覺舒服...
Whatever makes you feel comfortable...
呃 那個把襯衫脫了 好吧
Well, there goes a shirt. All right.
- 這是種選擇 - 呃...
- It's a choice. - Well...
但這是種錯誤的選擇
That's the wrong choice, though.
把襯衫穿上 那才是正確的...
Gotta wear a shirt. That's the one...
他正在離我越來越遠
He's walking away from me.
他可能是個壞員工
He might have been a bad hire.
誰玩得那麼開心啊
Who's having fun?
嘿 伙伴們
Hey, guys.
每個人看起來都很開心 這是個不錯的主意
Everybody seems very happy. This was a great idea.
嗯 我知道 但這也會成為一個問題
Yeah, I know. This could be an issue, though.
帶著孩子來工作 不是把孩子放在這裡工作
It is Bring Your Kids to Work Day, not Put Your Kids to Work Day.
他們不是在工作 他們把這個當做為一個遊戲
They're not working. They consider this playing.
我告訴他們停下 但一說他們就哭
I tried to tell them to stop, and they started crying.
他們已經裝了1200套了
They have boxed 1200 units already.
非專業... 1200套
Unethical... 1200?
- 是的 - 好吧 儘管如此 挺多產的
- Yeah. - Well, that's productive, though.
- 是的 - 他們看起來還挺開心的
- Yeah. - And they seem happy.
也許我應該讓他們多玩個10分鐘
Let them play another ten minutes, maybe.
我認為應該讓他們玩一整個中午
I say we let them play through lunch.
- 是的 從法律上講我得變下那個標牌 - 嗯
- Yeah. Legally I think I'll change the sign. - Yeah.
哦 哥們 就是它
Oh, boy. This is it.
走起 走起
Here we go. Here we go.
- 我們做到了 我們做夠十萬套了- 我做到了嗎
- We did it. We're at 100,000. - We did it?
- 是的 - 給我看看
- Yeah. - Let me see.
喔嚯嚯
Woo-hoo-hoo!
這主意太棒了
This is a great idea.
你們認為他會對此事不高興嗎
How do you think they mow this?
你認為我們不應該提前打電話嗎
Sure we shouldn't have called ahead?
不 他會喜歡的
No. He's gonna love it.
蛋糕和氣球 我們是不是做得太過了點
Cake and balloons. Don't think that's overdoing it?
不 我想他一定會為訂單提早三天完成
No. I think he's gonna
而感到興奮鼓舞的
be psyched the order's done three days early.
按照他的預計進程 他看到我們在這裡會瘋掉的
I think he's gonna be flipping out to see us out on his course.
如果他給我們會員資格的話 我是不會感到驚奇的
I wouldn't be surprised if he gives us a membership.
- 你沒開玩笑吧 - 沒有啊
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
天啊 我想要會員資格
Oh, my God. I want that.
太棒了
Yeah!
驚喜來啦 哈哈
Surprise. Ha, ha.
先生 我們已經完成了您的訂單
Sir, we finished your order
貨物正在等候船運
and it is ready to be shipped.
這消息真棒
Excellent news.
我們給您帶了個小蛋糕 上面寫著
We got you a little cake that says,
"感謝您對我們的信任"
"Thanks for believing in us!"
- 當然了 還有一些氣球 - 我們三個就是那個"我們"
- And some balloons of course. - We're the "us."
小伙子們 恭喜你們 成就非凡
Congratulations, boys. What an accomplishment.
- 謝謝您 - 謝謝
- Thank you. - Thanks.
我還以為得把訂單取消了呢
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to cancel that order.
他說的什麼
What'd he say?
- 聽著好像說的是"取消訂單" - 什麼
- Sounded like he said "cancel the order." - What?
- 取消什麼 - 取消訂單
- Cancel what? - Cancel the order.
我不需要它了
Don't need it.
- 不 等下 你這話起不了作用 - 你不能夠這麼做
- Wait, no. That doesn't work. - You can't do that.
- 我們財務負債了五百萬美元 - 我們還在做買賣呢
- We went 500 grand in the hole. - We were in business.
你要不買的話 我們就愧於一旦了
If you don't buy, we are ruined.
這可是筆五十萬美元的單子
It's a $500,000 order.
這就是他所謂的美國夢哈
The American dream and all that.
他就要擊球了 他僅僅是要擊球
He's gonna putt. He's just gonna putt.
- 他擊球了 - 你可以解釋下發生什麼了嗎
- He makes the putt. - Can you explain what's happening?
- 你為什麼要這麼做 - 嗯 是 好問題
- And why you're doing this? - Yeah, sure. Fair question.
小伙兒們 你們看 你們的過渡性融資一週後就要到期了...
You see, boys, in one week your bridge loan comes due...
但你們卻無力償還
and you won't be able to pay it.
你們的信貸員已經向我保證
And your loan officer has assured me
不會再貸給你們錢了
no extension will be granted.
到那個時候 你們的公司就會喪失抵押品贖回權...
At that moment, your company will go into foreclosure...
接著我會用美元以極低的價格在拍賣會上
and I will buy all of those units at auction
買光所有這些設備
for pennies on the dollar.
這比我從中國那裡買要便宜
Cheaper than I could have gotten them from the Chinese.
- 噢 我的天啊 - 這是真的嗎
- Oh, my fucking God. - I can't believe this.
另外 作為附加的紅利 你們的專利也將屬於我...
Anyway, as an added bonus, I will also own your patent...
而這兩位先生將
and these gentlemen here will
接管生產我們的新產品
take over manufacturing of our new product:
"浴室小伙伴"
The Shower Pal.
- 這名字更好聽點 - 是的
- It's a better name too. - It is.
- 真該死 - 我去
- Goddamn it. - Fucking hell.
噢 老爸  這真是個該死的遊戲
Oh, Dad, that is a hell of a fucking play.
我們應該給他們授以王冠
We should fit these guys for crowns
因為他們剛被莊重地調戲過
because they just got fucked royally.
雷克斯 不要在這裡賣弄
Rex. No call for this MTV showboating.
對於他們自己的失敗 他們心知肚明
They're aware of their defeat.
這種時候 不說話是更為有力的
In these moments, it's more impactful to be still.
既然如此 你所說的關於努力工作
What about that stuff about hard work
以及在美國白手起家的事情是真的嗎
and starting a company in America?
- 美國夢和努力工作 - 全是胡說八道嗎
- The American dream and hard work. - All bullshit?
你真的以為努力工作能夠創造財富嗎
You honestly think hard work creates wealth?
唯一能夠創造財富的就是財富本身
The only thing that creates wealth is wealth.
但是我們有 而你們沒有
And we have it. You don't.
好吧 好吧 你知道嗎
Okay. Okay. You know what?
- 別激動 別激動 - 我明白 喂
- Take it easy. Take it easy. - I got it. Hey.
聽著 老土霸 你不想與我們為敵 是嗎
Listen, bucko. You don't wanna make enemies out of us, okay?
喔 別激動 我不是衝著你來的
Whoa, easy. I didn't walk all up on you.
我每天都有新的敵人 這就是做生意
I make new enemies every day. It's called business.
小伙們 謝謝你們的到訪 祝你們今天過得愉快
Thank you, gentlemen, for stopping by. Have a lovely day.
雷克斯 把蛋糕拿走
Rex, get the cake.
有錢人都不要臉 去它媽的經濟收入超水準 混蛋
Rich motherfucking, overprivileged, fucking assholes.
人的正直去哪裡了
What happened to decency?
- 我就要失去我的房子了 - 是
- I'm gonna lose my house. - Yeah.
史黛西就要和我離婚了
Stacy's gonna divorce me.
她要嫁給一個花花公子了
She's gonna marry some dude.
我以後去個麥當勞也要被人監視了
I'll have supervised visits at McDonald's.
去它的麥當勞
Fucking McDonald's.
我們過去都在想什麼
What were we thinking?
怎麼把賭注下到他們身上了呢
Who bets on themselves?
我們為什麼那樣做
Why did we do that?
- 你說什麼 - 你就是那時候說服我的那個人
- What? - You're the one who talked me into it.
我那時候中立
I was on the fence.
我們被耍了 我們的員工被耍了
We're fucked! Our employees are fucked.
他們呢 盧佩呢
What about them? What about Lupe?
這只是一個問題
This is just a problem.
我們所需要做的就是想出這個問題的解決辦法
That means all we gotta do is come up with a solution.
我們可以把想法寫到這塊板上
We'll put some ideas up on the board.
這正是我要說的 說做就做 來吧
That's what I'm talking about. Here we go. Let's go.
沒有主意才是最糟糕的
No idea's a bad idea.
- 誰先開始說 - 我來
- Who's gonna start us off? - I got it.
- 庫爾特你來 - 把這幫畜生宰了
- Kurt. - Kill these motherfuckers.
- 不 不 - 宰了他們 對
- No, no. - Murder! Yes.
- 你不必把它寫下來 - 宰了他們
- You don't need to write that down. - Kill them.
我們去宰了他們 我要把他們弄死
Let's fucking kill them! I want them dead!
宰了他們
Kill them.
切開他們的腦袋再用力扔到一邊去...
We open up their brains and shove them...
然後干他們的頭蓋兒
Then we fuck the skulls!
那種快感越來越強烈 尼克
I'm getting that taste, Nick.
他們死啦
They're fucking dead!
我們再來一遍
We're fucking doing it again!
這就是芝加哥處理方式
That's the Chicago way!
芝加哥處理方式
Chicago way!
把他們的腦袋切開 我想弄死他一家
Cut them open. I want his family dead.
我要把他的房子點了 我就能拿到棒球棒了
I want his house burned down, and I'll get a baseball bat.
- 來吧 伙伴 來吧 - 干他們的頭蓋兒
- Come on, man, come on. - Fuck their skulls!
- 來啊 - 來啊
- Come on. - Come on.
我們去宰了他們
We'll fucking kill them.
如果我們要對自身進行了解的話
If we've learned one thing about ourselves,
那麼首先應該明白的就是我們不是殺手
it's that we're not murderers.
殺了他們怎麼能讓我們的錢回來呢
How does killing them get us our money?
你什麼意思
What do you mean?
你帶走他們的器官 然後拿它們到黑市上賣
You harvest their organs, sell them on the black market.
嚴肅點 伙伴們 這樣是無濟於事的
Be fucking serious. Come on. This is not helpful.
我們要認真地思考下
Think seriously.
你說得對 很多事情都有人做過了
You're right. There's other things people have done.
- 得有秘密計劃 - 為了我們的錢
- There's plots. - For money.
電影速度的秘密計劃
The plot of the movie Speed.
對 就這樣 把炸彈放在巴士上
Yes, there you go. Put a bomb on a bus.
所以我們得操縱住一輛巴士
So we'll rig a bus so that
當它時速低於五十米每小時時 讓它引爆
when it goes below 50 miles an hour, it blows up.
- 什麼濫主意 - 你說沒主意才是最糟糕的
- What the fuck is that? - You said no idea was a bad idea.
我錯了 這主意太爛了 電影很爛 你也很爛
I was wrong. That idea sucks, the movie sucks and so do you.
這個電影讓我們想起了桑迪·布洛克
That movie introduced us to Sandy Bullock.
去你的 我愛桑德拉·布洛克 我已熱血沸騰
Fuck you! I love Sandra Bullock! I'm running hot.
抱歉 我已經熱火沸騰了
I'm sorry. I'm running hot.
整件事情都他媽讓我心煩意亂
The whole fucking thing's got me upset.
把筆給我 我會想到更好的辦法
Give me the marker, I'll get a better idea.
想要筆嗎 給我五十萬美元
Want the marker? Give me $500,000,
那才是我們需要的
that's what we need.
想要那支筆的贖金嗎
Gonna hold the marker ransom?
你愛怎麼說怎麼說吧
Call it what you want.
我需要五十萬美元
I need a half a million dollars.
我需要的不是什麼鬼主意或在這裡閒扯淡
I don't need shit ideas and a bunch of hot air.
來吧
Come on.
黛爾
Dale.
- 嘣嘣 筆掉了 - "拐騙罪"
- Boom. Marker drop. - "Kidnaping."
這是"綁架"
That's "kidnapping."
你說的是多了個P的那個詞
With one more P it is.
這個是"拐騙罪"
That's "kidnaping."
管你他媽怎麼拼呢
However the fuck you spell it.
你知道我在說什麼 就是綁架 走起
You know what I'm talking about. Kidnapping. Come on.
等下 這主意不錯
Wait a second. That's a fucking great idea.
先想想 首先 我們要綁架雷克斯
Think about it. First of all, we kidnap Rex.
- 然後向伯特要錢 - 贖金
- We get money from Bert. - Ransom money.
如此我們還省事了
We save the business.
也沒有人會死
No one has to die.
- 沒有人會受傷 - 他是伯特的孩子
- Nobody gets hurt. - He is the kid of Bert.
對 而且他年齡也不算很小
Right, but he's not super young.
這樣做不會顯得太白痴
So it's not super douchey and shit.
而且危害也不是最大
It's not all molesty and shit.
你們知道如何實施綁架嗎
What do you know about executing a kidnapping?
- 你什麼意思 你只要... - 用拉鏈綁
- What do you mean? You just... - You get zip ties.
你們關於綁架一無所知
You don't know shit about kidnapping.
好吧 我們知道的不多
Okay, we don't know a ton.
但是敢打賭 我們知道有人深諳其道
But I bet we know someone that does.
- 誰 - 壞蛋瓊斯
- Who? - Motherfucker Jones.
- 哦 天啊 - 去找他不好嗎
- Oh, Jesus. - Wouldn't it be good to see him?
我們不會去找混蛋瓊斯
We're not gonna go see Motherfucker Jones
因為我們也不會"綁架"任何人
because we're not gonna "kidnape" anyone.
得了吧 這個傢伙在對問題的處理上是個蠢貨
Come on, this guy's a master business prick.
他正處於事業的巔峰 我們得明白...
He's at the top of his game. We need to figure out...
伙伴們 看看這都是什麼
Boy, look what we got.
是用記號筆寫的嗎
Is that a Sharpie?
等下 記號筆怎麼會在那裡呢
Hang on. What was a Sharpie doing there?
你把它放那裡的
You put it there.
我的確把它放到那裡了
I did put it on there.
是你負責管理記號筆的
You're in charge of marker distribution.
我知道我就是那個看記號筆的人
I know I'm the marker guy.
現在擦不掉了
Permanently on the board now.
這讓我想出了一個方法 笨蛋們
This illustrates my point, idiots.
我們需要找到一個合法人
We need to find somebody who's legitimate.
我們需要找到一個能夠讓我們的公司回來的人
We need to find someone who can get us our company back.
嗨 尼克...
Hello, Nick...
一個傢伙是救了我性命...
guy who saved my life...
一個傢伙是上了我老婆
guy who fucked my wife.
那是爭吵 僅僅是爭吵 我沒有上她
It was a blow job. It was a blow job, only. Didn't fuck her.
你收到我的郵件了嗎
You got my e-mail?
收到了 而且我被它逗得樂不可支
I did. And I was very amused by it.
我知道伯特·漢森
I know Bert Hanson.
我希望你們能夠重創他
I like the cut of his jib.
但是我欣賞他把你們三個白痴
And I admire the way he bent you three idiots
玩弄於股掌並讓你們死得明白的行為方式
over a barrel and showed you the 50 states.
- 明白了 跟你說過這是個俗語 - 哇哦
- See? Told you it was a saying. - Wow.
尼克 現在回答我幾個問題
Now, Nick, just tell me something.
你為什麼在對方還沒保證
Why would you start production...
給你墊付至少百分之三十五的製造成本之前
without at least a guarantee of 35 percent down...
就開始生產了呢
to cover manufacturing costs?
我是說 你為什麼那麼做
I mean, why would you do that?
- 他在講笑話嗎 - 有什麼搞笑的事情嗎
- Is he telling a joke? - Is something funny?
我們以為我們遇到好人了...
We assumed that we were dealing with somebody who was ethical...
不 你回答錯了 正確的答案是因為...
No, that's the wrong answer. The right answer is because...
你們都是白痴
you're all fucking morons.
哥們 他提出自己的觀點了 對嗎
Boy, he shined a light on that, didn't he?
你說得對 你說得很對
That's true. You're absolutely right.
你以為我是一個很差勁的老闆
You thought I was such a bad boss.
但我可不這麼認為
But, I don't know,
我認為也許你們把自己的公司經營得一敗塗地...
I think running your own company into the ground...
毀掉你們員工的生計可能會更加糟糕
ruining the livelihood of your employees is maybe a bit worse.
你覺得呢
What do you think?
你說得對
That's fair.
我是不是應該在你們打電話的時候做記錄呢
Should I be on the phone if I'm taking notes?
我完全聽不到他說的任何話
I'm not getting any of what he's saying.
都是一些誇張的問題
It's just a lot of rhetorical questions.
那麼你想從我這裡得到點什麼 尼克
So, what do you want from me, Nick?
無意冒犯 我想你知道他是個什麼樣的人
With all due respect, you know what makes a guy like that tick.
如果你能給我們提些
So if you could give us some advice on
如何把我們的錢弄回來的建議的話...
how to get our money back...
我會在你下次假釋聽證會上表現得特別棒
I will play real nice at your next parole hearing.
這聽起來感覺怎麼樣
How does that sound?
- 你會為我做那些事情嗎 - 是的 我會
- You would do that for me? - Yes, I would.
好的 我想我能幫你
Okay. I think I can help you.
他要幫我們嗎
He's gonna help?
好 我帶了筆記本 我帶了筆記本
Okay, I got a notepad. I got a notepad.
從法律的角度上講...
From a legal standpoint...
"法律的角度"
"Legal standpoint."
...你的選擇是...
...your options are...
...吃屎去吧
...jack fucking shit.
我聽到了"傑克·維茨" 是律師嗎
I heard "Jack Leibowitz." Is that an attorney?
我會寫下來的
I'll write that down.
能告訴我們他的聯絡方式嗎
Can we get his contact info?
即使你們有錢跟他對簿公堂
Even if you had the money to fight him in the courts...
他的律師也會在你們三個小嘍囉
his lawyers are just gonna file motions and continuances...
燒光腦細胞之後
long after you three pissant little fuckups...
不斷申訴
have blown your tiny little brains out.
你是說一切已成定局了嗎
You saying nothing can be done?
不是 我是說你們屁事也乾不成
No, I said there's nothing you can do.
想要力挽狂瀾有很多出路 但你們屁事也乾不成
There's plenty that could be done, but you won't do it.
- 你想知道為什麼嗎 - 不想
- And do you wanna know why? - No, not really.
- 因為你們是沒蛋的傢伙 - 懂了
- Because you have no balls. - I see.
你們的爹也沒蛋
And your fathers had no balls.
你們都是一群沒蛋的人養的兒子
You are all a product of generations of ball-less men...
懦弱無能 不敢揭竿而起
who were too weak or too frightened to stand up
奪回屬於自己的東西
and take what was theirs.
總有一天 你們會一命嗚呼
And one day, you will pass on...
把你空空蕩蕩 皺皺巴巴的陰囊留給你們可憐的兒子
your empty, shriveled sacs to your own pitiful offspring.
我聽不見啊 他在說什麼
I can't hear. What is he talking about?
說我們的陰囊 大部分是
Our nut sacs, mostly.
怎麼會說到這個
How'd that come up?
你怎麼不提綁架的事
Why don't you pitch him the kidnapping?
別提綁架這事了
Let the kidnapping go.
- 快說綁架的事 - 有點種 行嗎
- Pitch him the kidnapping. - Show some balls, all right?
想看蛋蛋 去綁架個人來看吧
Wanna see balls? Kidnap someone.
然後你鋃鐺入獄 會有很多蛋蛋在你眼前晃的
You'll end up in here. You'll see plenty of balls on your forehead.
為什麼在我眼前晃
Why are they on my forehead?
- 丁丁是在我頭上嗎 - 胡說八道
- Was the dick on top of my head? - Makes no sense.
哦我倒過來了
Oh, I'm upside down.
絕逼是的 你的臉要被幹了
You sure are. Your face is getting fucked.
媽蛋
Motherfucker.
你打算用那筆贖金挽救你們的事業
So y'all plan to use the ransom to save your business.
- 正事 就是這樣的 - 我們是這樣打算的
- Exactly, yeah. That's it. - That's what we're hoping.
你能告訴這兩個傻逼那樣有多傻逼嗎 謝謝
Will you tell these idiots how stupid that is, please?
我喜歡
I like it.
- 太棒了 看見了吧 - 我就知道他喜歡
- Nice. See? - I knew he'd like it.
你總得努力讓公司繼續運轉
You're doing what you need to to keep your business going.
我早就夢想開家自己的公司
I had a dream for a long time to get my own business.
就是啊
Yeah.
我想開自己的莓果冰淇淋店
I wanted to open my own Pinkberry.
- 你他媽的笑什麼 - 我以為你在搞笑
- What the fuck is the chuckles about? - Oh, I thought you were joking.
你知道有多少妞排隊買那個嘎吱嘎吱船長
See how many crackers line up to
上面蓋著一坨冰凍的翔
get that Captain Crunch-covered freezing shit?
我一週吃三次 我超愛莓果冰淇淋
I eat it three times a week. I love Pinkberry.
超牛逼的
Hey, that's awesome.
- 你喜歡莓果冰淇淋 - 我有乳糖不耐症
- You like Pinkberry? - I'm lactose intolerant.
- 好吧 - 你長了個非洲裔美國人的肚子嗎
- Right. - You got an African-American belly?
- 黑人就不能吃乳糖 - 這樣啊 好吧
- Because black people suffer from lactose. - Oh, okay, good, well...
- 我們有點親戚關係 - 不錯啊
- We got some kind of kinship. - Yeah, cool, man.
- 拉得出屎嗎 - 這個可以
- Stool soft? - It can be.
- 屁股軟嗎 - 挺軟的
- Bottom tender. - Yeah, bottom's fine.
如果有人搶了我的莓果冰淇淋
If somebody took my Pinkberry,
我不會善罷甘休的
I wouldn't take that sitting down.
- 你得揭竿而起 - 我會把那傻貨長的劈成兩半
- You would fight. - I will cut a motherfucker in half.
你不會綁架的
You wouldn't kidnap someone
因為你根本辦不成
because you can't successfully pull it off.
說個講綁架的電影來聽聽
Name me a kidnapping movie...
而且結局是綁匪沒翹辮子也沒坐牢
where the kidnappers weren't dead or incarcerated at the end.
- 朝九晚五 你個沒屁眼的 - 朝九晚五
- 9 to 5, asshole. - 9 to 5.
- 那再說一個 - 你說了一個就行的
- Name me two movies, then. - You said name one.
- 我剛剛就說了一個 - 朝九晚五這個電影...
- I nailed one right on you. - 9 to 5 was this movie...
我知道朝九晚五
I know what the fuck 9 to 5 is.
是講那個大奶子的白人婊子
It's about the white bitch with the big titties.
是啊
Yeah.
她雖然人老珠黃 奶子還是不錯的
She got old, the titties stayed young.
我不會看了朝九晚五就去綁票
I'm not gonna kidnap someone based on 9 to 5.
- 那是因為你是簡·方達[著名演員] - 你就是膽小鬼
- That's because you Jane Fonda. - You're the scaredy-cat one.
你就是最沒用的 老是拖拖拉拉
You're always the last to man up. You're dragging your feet.
你都不想參與你在這幹嘛
Why are you here if you're not gonna participate?
首先 如果這裡有人長了腦子的話
First of all, if anyone,
就是我 我是莉莉·湯姆林[美國女影星]
I'm the smart one. I'm Lily Tomlin.
我不想跟你說了
But I won't have this conversation.
算了吧 老子是莉莉·湯姆林
Please, I'm Lily Tomlin, if anybody is.
坐在大椅子上 鳥都不鳥大衛·O·拉塞爾[90年代喜劇演員]
Sitting in the big chair, giving David O. Russell shit.
就是啊 他有點上道了 你是莉莉·湯姆林
Yeah, he's got the 'tude. You're Fonda, man.
你是方達
You're Jane Fonda.
那你就是桃莉·芭頓
That makes you Dolly Parton.
太好了 這女人自娛自樂啊
Great. Woman's got her own theme park.
- 她簡直是國寶 - 倆國寶
- She's a national treasure. - Two national treasures.
我能問你們這些殖民者一個問題嗎
Can I pose a question to you colonizers?
猴年馬月的事了
Happened a long time ago.
你要怎麼綁架一個人
How do you kidnap somebody without them knowing...
還不讓他知道自己被綁架了
they've been kidnapped?
- 好的 - 你少裝蒜了 你又沒綁架過
- Okay. - You smarten up, and you don't even do it.
他是個黑人獅身人面像 我喜歡
He's a black sphinx. I like it.
他給我們指點迷津了
He threw a riddle our way.
- 你怎麼... - 巫術 巫術怎麼樣
- How do you...? - Voodoo. Voodoo?
我可以告訴你們答案
I can give you the answers.
- 五萬塊 - 不是吧
- Fifty thousand. - No.
- 辦不到 - 六百怎樣
- We can't. - Six hundred?
你就不該開莓果冰淇淋店 不好意思了
You should not run a Pinkberry. Sorry.
- 這簡直是最奇怪的溝通方式 - 我們沒錢
- The weirdest negotiating style. - We don't have money.
我們到這裡來就是因為我們身無分文 我們破產了
You know, we're here because we have zero dollars. We're broke.
媽蛋 把手錶給我
Fuck it. Give me the watch.
- 不要 - 手錶給他
- Nope. - Give him your watch.
我才不給他 這可是豪雅表
I'm not giving him this. This is a Tag Heuer.
這就是個沒戴手錶的手腕
This is a wrist without a watch.
給他吧 錢財這種東西生不帶來死不帶去
Come on. It's just material things. Can't take it with you.
既然你給我們出餿主意 我就借給你
You can borrow it while you tell us a shitty plan.
好吧
All right.
給他下藥
Slip him a mickey.
還我手錶
Give me the watch back.
你半夜溜進他家
You sneak into his crib at night.
看看他睡覺之前都喝什麼
Find out whatever his beverage of choice is before he goes to bed.
在飲料裡下點藥 隨時把他搞定
You slip the mickey in the beverage. Knock him out nice and easy.
他爹不給錢 你們就別讓他醒過來
And you keep that bitch sedated until Daddy pays up.
這主意還湊合 但可不值一隻瑞士手錶
It's not a crazy idea, but it's not worth a Swiss watch.
- 能行得通的 - 太棒了 絕逼好主意
- That could work. - That's great. That makes total sense.
- 他又看不見我們長什麼樣 - 我們就像幽靈一樣 根本不存在
- He doesn't see our faces. - We're ghosts. We don't even exist.
你說的"藥"是什麼藥
When you say "mickey... "?
一種約會是強姦姑娘用的藥 你上哪裡搞的
A date-rape drug. Where do you get those?
- 我上哪裡搞 - 是啊
- Where do I get them? - Yeah.
因為我是黑鬼我就知道上哪裡搞這種藥
Because of the hue of my skin I know where to get date-rape drugs?
- 這事是你提的 - 你眼裡在說N詞
- You brought up the date-raping. - You got N word in your eyes.
- 你為什麼要說N詞 - 三K黨眼
- Why are your eyes saying the N word? - Klan eyes.
- 你才有三K黨眼 - 你眼睛做過檢查嗎
- You've got Klan eyes. - You ever take a eye test?
- 做過 - 你選的都是K
- Yes. - All you pick out is the K.
- 每個字母都能看見 - 他是有三K黨眼
- I see every letter. - He does have Klan eyes.
床單後面你都能看見
You can see them poking out behind that sheet.
太荒唐了... 太討厭的
It's just ridic... I can't... It's so upsetting.
我問你個問題吧
Let me ask you a question.
你被朱莉亞強姦的時候
When you got raped by Julia,
她用什麼弄昏你的 笑氣嗎
what did she use to knock you out? Laughing gas?
- 對喔 - 這樣行
- Oh, right. - That'll work.
- 這下有意思了 - 你有辦公室鑰匙嗎
- That's interesting. - You have keys to the office?
- 沒有 但我知道密碼 - 很好
- No, but I know the code. - Yes.
好吧 又來了
Okay. You did it again.
鄭重聲明 我沒有種族歧視
For the record, I am not racist.
你最棒了 太感謝你
You're the best. Thank you very much.
- 撤 再會 - 見到你很高興
- Let's go. See you. - Good to see you.
還真是大有裨益啊 能把表還我嗎
Surprisingly helpful. Any way I can get the watch back?
滾 簡·方達
Fuck out of here, Jane Fonda.
這傢伙真壯 你沒辦法以一敵三 對吧
That's a tough one. And you can't fuck all three, right?
- 辦不到 - 遊戲不是這樣玩的
- You cannot. - Not the game. Okay.
然後我會跟彼得結婚 殺了博比 上格雷格
Well, then I would marry Peter, kill Bobby, and fuck Greg.
- 我也要這麼幹 - 是嗎
- That's what I'd do too. - Yeah?
- 我覺得只能這麼玩 - 有道理啊
- I think that's the only way to play it. - It makes sense.
- 怎麼樣啊 - 很順利啊
- How'd you do? - I did great.
我買了很多 我覺得我們這次得小心行事
I got extra supplies. I think we gotta be more careful this time.
絕對的 太聰明了
Absolutely. So smart.
我買了本雜誌 可以拼綁架的紙條
I got a magazine to cut up the ransom note.
- 我們不能手寫啊 - 聰明
- Can't be writing it by hand. - Smart.
- 新娘雜誌
Bride Again Magazine?
如果條子查這些字母是哪裡來的
To throw the cops off if they start snooping
我們就可以瞞過他們
to figure out where the letters came from.
- 多拉探險家對講機 - 牛逼啊
- Dora the Explorer walkie-talkies? - Awesome.
- 這又不是間間諜設備專賣店 就是個便利商店 - 你沒想過我們就用手機嗎
- It's not a spy store. It's a convenience store. - Didn't wanna just use our phones?
用手機吧
Let's use our phones.
這樣我們說了什麼做了什麼條子都能查到
They make a record of everything that we say and do.
- 你看不看新聞的啊 - 不好意思
- Do you watch the news? - My apologies.
嘿 歐巴馬 我要闖進我以前的辦公室啦
Hey, Obama. I'm breaking into my old office.
犯事的只有我們三人 又不是我們對著美帝
It's just the three of us doing this, not us and the NSA.
我是想幫忙
I'm trying to help us out.
- 你買剪刀了嗎 - 買了
- Did you get scissors? - I got some scissors.
- 沒見你買橡膠手套啊 - 太貴了
- I don't see any latex gloves in here. - They're, like, super expensive.
- 多少錢 - 九刀一副
- How much? - Nine bucks a pair.
- 太荒唐了 - 就是說啊
- That's ridiculous. - Right?
我就交代了你要買橡膠手套
It's the only thing you went in there to buy.
她辦公室裡一堆手套呢
She's got a ton of gloves in her office.
用那些就行了
We'll just use those.
你得有手套才能進去 才能不留下指紋
You need them to get inside, so we don't leave fingerprints.
對啊 你個傻逼 你不知道嗎
That's right. You dummy. Don't you know that?
你知道我們可以怎麼做嗎 用我包裡的手套
Know what we can do? We can use my golf gloves in my bag.
他高爾夫包裡有手套
He's got gloves in his golf bag.
別雞蛋裡挑骨頭 我想幫忙呢
Don't poke holes in everything. I'm trying to help out.
伙伴們 我們又重出江湖了
Guys, the team's back together.
我把風
I call lookout.
看見有人進來我會告訴你的
And I will let you know if I see Swiper.
他好了 走吧
Nice. Let's go.
裡面怎麼樣 伙伴們
How we doing in there, guys?
我來 我來 我來
I got it. I got it. I got it.
都很好 外面怎麼樣 尼克
All good. How are things out there, Nick?
沒事 你能別朝著對講機喊我們名字嗎
Things are good. Hey, can you not say my name over the radio, please?
- 為什麼啊 - 別的頻道上可能有人叫尼克啊
- Why not? - Could be somebody on the frequency.
對喔 有道理 真聰明
Oh, yeah. It's a good point. Very smart.
好了 那我們用亨德里克斯
There you go. That's using the old Hendricks brain.
姓也別叫
And there's the last name.
- 我們得想個暗號啊 - 就是啊
- We should come up with code names. - Absolutely.
尼克 你想要什麼暗號
Nick, where you landing on code names?
你別再叫我名字我就很高興了
I'd love it if you'd stop saying my name.
- 拿上笑氣就趕快閃人吧 - 收到
- Just get the gas and get out here. - Roger that.
"刀鋒劍士"搞定目標
The Blade has acquired the target.
- 是用的劍嗎 - 那是我的暗號啊 尼克
- Was that "The Blade"? - That's my code name, Nick.
我們不需要暗號 大家都知道誰在說話
We don't need code names. Everybody knows who's talking.
聽起來很酷啊 我們再想兩個吧
They're sounding pretty cool, so let's try to land on a couple.
我馬上就能給你想一個暗號
I'm gonna think up one real quick and lay it on you.
我想到了"獅子王" 我就是"獅子王"
I'm coming in at you with The Majestic Lion. I'm gonna be The Majestic Lion.
現在是我們在說話
Now we're talking.
我不會那樣叫你的
Not gonna call you that.
你真混蛋 你最好給我想一個好理由
That's a bummer there. I'm gonna need a reason as to why.
因為你不是叢林之貓 簡直傻逼
Because you're not a jungle cat, and it's stupid as shit.
- 有道理 - 接的好
- Fair point. - Good catch.
我們得給他想一個暗號
We should come up with one for him.
- 聖·尼克怎麼樣 - 你他媽喊我四次了
- How about St. Nick? - You've said my name four fucking times.
你們回車上 我們就能回家了
If you could come back out to the car, we can go home.
對了 我把"獅子"去掉怎麼樣
You know what? What if I drop the "Lion"?
- 有人來了 有人來了 - 只要光叫"王"嗎
- Somebody's here. Somebody's here. - Just The Majestic?
我太愛了 我喜歡
I love that. I like that.
別再說暗號的事了
Shut up about the code names.
一群人剛進了停車場
A bunch of people just pulled up into the parking lot.
嘿 別老按著按鈕
Hello. Get your thumb off the butt...
天啊
Oh, my God.
剛有個辣妞進了朱莉亞的停車位
Real hot chick just pulled into Julia's parking spot.
我猜朱莉亞要進大樓了
I think Julia's headed into the building.
把爪子從按鈕上拿開...
If you'd get your thumb off the fucking button and...
操 倆傻逼
Fuck. Fucking idiots.
好吧 反正不關我的事
Well, you know what?
不是我的錯 不是我的錯
It's not my fault. It's not my goddamn fault.
我又沒做犯法的事 我可以開車溜之大吉了
I haven't done a thing illegal. I can just drive out of here.
直接回家
I can just drive right home.
不行 不能這樣做
No, I can't do that. I can't do that.
倆傻逼會出賣我的
They'll just fucking tell on me.
好了 我們朝你那邊去了 那個妞剛離開車位了 我的天啊 我的天啊
All right, we're on our way to you. Chickens have left the pot. My God, my God.
- 我覺得那是雞籠 - 什麼
- The coop, I think. - What?
"我的天 我的天"聽著像個不錯的暗號
The "my God, my God" does sounds like a thing.
我了個去
Oh, shit.
你把吃的放那邊吧
Why don't you set the food up over there?
我們可以把椅子圍成一個圈
And we'll circle these chairs around.
黛爾
Dale?
庫爾特
Kurt.
神吶 保佑我們
God, grant us...
我操 是邪教 他媽的遇到邪教徒了
Oh, shit. It's a cult. It's a fucking cult.
...我們無法改變的性癮...
...about our sex addiction that we cannot change...
- 性癮 - 是性癮 是啊
- Sex addiction. - It's a sex addiction. Yeah.
巧妙
Neat.
我以你們為榮 每一個人 你們今天能來到這裡
So proud of you, every one of you, for being here today.
媽蛋
Shit.
有什麼事嗎
How's it going?
嗨 我...
Hi. It's going...
你知道的
You know.
我有麻煩了
I'm in trouble.
- 省省吧 - 好吧
- Save it. - Okay.
...他們這週遇上了一些事
...something that happened to them this week.
我發現這位先生在你們的大廳遊蕩
Found this gentleman loitering out in your hall.
操 尼克被發現了
Oh, shit. Nick got busted.
他說他有麻煩了
Says he knows he's in trouble.
- 是啊 - 我們都有麻煩
- Yeah. - We're all in trouble.
你不用害怕 你在這裡很安全
You don't have to be afraid. You're safe here.
好吧
Okay.
不好意思我遲到了 怎麼樣啊 兄弟
Sorry I'm late. What's up, brother?
托比 你幫這年輕人
Toby, why don't you grab a chair
拿個椅子這樣他就能加入我們了
and bring it in so this young man can join us?
好啊...
Yeah...
- 天啊... - 你叫什麼名字 親愛的
- Boy... - What's your name, honey?
我叫...
I am...
我叫布萊斯頓
I am Blanston.
- 你好 布萊斯頓 - 你好
- Hi, Blanston. - Hi.
他還說他不喜歡暗號
For a guy not into code names...
- 好危險啊 - 大膽的選擇啊
- Big swing. - Bold choice.
- 我喜歡 - 就是啊
- And I love it. - Yeah.
- 很高興小組裡有了新人 - 感謝大家
- It's nice to have fresh blood in the group. - Appreciate it.
- 新來的小帥哥 - 嘿
- Fresh, cute blood. - Hey.
慢慢來 朱莉亞
Easy, Julia. Blanston,
能跟我們說說你是怎麼進到恢復小組的嗎 布萊斯頓
would you like to share with us what's led you into recovery?
好吧 我是有個很大的問題
Well, okay. I do have a very big problem.
困擾我很久了 很久了
Just been hitting it hard. I've been hitting it hard.
他以為他是在戒酒互助會呢
He thinks he's in an AA meeting.
經常和一群人鬼混
Getting together with the guys.
每次都不省人事
Oftentimes, ending up just face down.
一次接著一次 有的時候甚至還要加倍
Chugging one after the other. Sometimes double-fisted, just:
你知道吧 知道我在說什麼吧
You know? You know what I'm talking about.
所以你的性癮 是天生的同性戀性癮嗎
So your sexual addiction, it's homosexual in nature?
我的性癮 我的...
My sex addiction? My sex addiction is...
你剛說什麼來著
And then what did you say?
- 你喜歡上男人 - 不是 我喜歡女人
- You like to fuck guys. - No. My sex addiction is to ladies.
- 哦 - 我對女人很上癮
- Oh. - You know. I'm addicted to women.
真無聊
Boring.
- 操 我想尿尿 - 什麼
- Oh, fuck, I have to piss. - What?
我想尿尿 我很緊張 不好意思
I have to piss. I'm nervous. I'm sorry.
- 去吧 去尿 - 聲音會很大的
- Go, go, just pee. - It's gonna make too much noise.
不會的 去廁所裡尿
No, no, just dip your dick into the toilet.
- 坐著尿 好吧 - 是啊 去吧
- Oh, sit down and do it? Okay. - Yeah, yeah.
- 搆不到 - 什麼
- It doesn't reach. - What?
搆不到啊 應該搆得到嗎
It doesn't reach. Should it reach?
我不知道應不應該
I mean, I don't know if it's about "should," but...
- 我要把座墊拿起來了 - 對 把座墊拿起來
- I'll put the seat up. - Yeah, put the seat up...
- ...對準馬桶尿 - 哦 天啊
- ...and just dip your butt in the bowl. - Oh, my God.
好了
There we go.
- 操 對不起 - 沒事
- Oh, shit, sorry. - It's okay.
- 抱歉 我小便後都要衝一衝 - 沒事
- Sorry, I always flush. - It's all right.
好了 我現在要洗手
Okay, I'm just gonna wash my hands.
不 你為什麼要洗手
No. Why are you gonna wash your hands?
- 為什麼 - 我哪次不洗手啦
- Why? - I always wash my hands.
- 你戴了手套的 - 被尿浸濕了
- You have gloves on. - Stuff gets under there.
好吧 別把動靜搞太大
Fine, just be quiet. Okay, okay.
就洗一下 不洗總感覺渾身不自在
Let me just wash them. I'll feel better.
哇靠 黛爾 住手
Oh, my God, Dale, stop.
我們是在偷窺 你好歹專業點
There's literally no element of sneak in anything you're doing.
- 沒那麼明顯吧 - 我也要尿一泡
- It's gross not to. - I gotta go now too.
- 你也要去? - 嗯
- You gotta go? - Yeah.
你灑手上沒有
Do you golf with the other hand...?
別吹口哨
Don't whistle.
沒辦法 只有這樣我才能尿出來
I have to. The only way to get this train going.
- 聽著 - 你幹嘛也衝
- Listen... - Why did you flush?
- 條件反射 - 為什麼
- It just happens. - Why?
- 這是個好習慣 - 扯淡
- It's a good habit. - Shit.
- 那是...? - 尼瑪 她過來了 躲起來
- What is...? - Shit. She's coming. Hide.
不過 曾經有一次 曾經有一次
But there was once, though. There was once...
大爺的 如果你們能保密的話
Oh, boy. If this is safe in here,
我倒想說出來和你們分享
I'd love to shake this out and share it.
情況有變 別掉下來打到我
Something must've happened. Don't fall on me.
別擔心 我在社區活動中心練過跑酷
Don't worry. I took a parkour class at the community center.
他把她弄回去了
Oh, he got her to go back.
- 我那時還是個孩子 - 多大
- I was a boy. - How old were you?
- 忘了 只記得很小 - 十四歲?
- I don't know. Young. - Fourteen?
差不多吧 兩個十四歲的男孩在露營的時候
I think we were. Two 14-year-old boys at camp...
不知道怎麼的
and not knowing what we're doing...
就絞在一起了
and just wrestling.
絞基露營 十四歲
Ooh. Wrestling camp. Fourteen.
相當精彩
Nice.
他說的是真的嗎
Is he telling the truth?
我不知道 不過如果是真的
I... I don't know. But, I mean, if he is...
-很適合他 對吧 - 必須的 眾望所歸
- Good for him, right? - Absolutely. That's great.
你們有沒有穿緊身熱辣連體衣
Did you guys wear those tight little onesies?
運動衫?
Singlets?
- 是這樣叫的嗎? - 對 運動衫
- Is that what they're called? - That's right. Singlets.
穿上緊身的彈性衣
Tight little spandex
龜頭的輪廓會更加清晰嗎?
offering a clear little outline of, say, a circumcised helmet?
- 我勒個擦 - 我有熱血沸騰嗎?
- Oh, boy. - Am I getting warm?
好了 也許該其他人分享了
Okay, maybe someone else should share.
- 不不不 我們再談談那東西 - 什麼意思
- No, no, no. Let's go to the unit. - Sorry?
那個地方看起來...?
What was the unit like on this little b...?
是青筋暴起的還是光滑的
Was it veiny? Smooth?
像小的高領毛衣還是食蟻獸
Little turtleneck? Anteater?
我 我也不清楚 很平常
I just... I don't know. Pretty normal.
初出茅廬的老二?
Starter penis?
我不想說得這麼直接 不過
Not the words I would've used, but...
團隊裡有個基佬也是很不錯的 對吧
It's good to have a gay friend in your group too, you know?
- 生命因此而精彩 - 沒錯
- It makes us more colorful. - Yeah.
那東西有沒有成功塞進你嘴裡
Now, did this penis ever, at any point,
哪怕是一部分
find its way into your mouth?
- 我的天 - 朱莉亞 別這樣
- Jesus. - Julia, no.
- 你不要再玩兒這套把戲了 - 什麼把戲
- You're not gonna pull this stunt again. - What stunt?
提前結束分享會
Stopping a meeting early
這樣她就可以想辦法找個基佬來一發
so she can try to flip another gay.
- 真的? - 得不到的總想要 說的就是她
- Really? - She always wants what she can't have.
聽著 沒激動 好吧? 他都不是基佬
Listen, relax, okay? He's not even gay.
十四歲的時候有一根雞巴擺在
He had one cock at 14
他面前他都沒有吹一管
and it hasn't made its way to his mouth yet.
你要是讓我說完
Well, if you'd let me finish...
這樣說來你吹了一管
So you did eat that cock.
你不就是想問我有沒有吹
You're asking if I sucked it?
我知道你吹了
I know you sucked it.
我只是想聽你親口說
I just wanna hear you say it.
- 布萊斯頓你沒必要說出來 - 閉嘴
- Blanston, you don't have to say it. - Shut your mouth.
- 閉嘴 讓他說 你吹沒吹 - 快說吹了
- Shut up and let him share. You ate it? - Please say yes.
你想知道我有沒有吹一管?
You wanna know if I ate that dick?
你有沒有吹那管 就像炸彈直衝雲霄
Did you suck that cock like a Bomb Pop down to the blue?
- 你想知道答案? - 給我說
- You want the answer? - Give it to me.
我把他的老二和蛋蛋都塞進了嘴裡
I ate that dick, balls,
還添了他濕潤的菊花
and licked that kid's sweaty asshole.
這他媽就對了 你做了
Damn right you did
因為你就是一個貨真價實的基佬
because you are awesomely gay.
我是超級基佬 從來就沒有直過
I'm super gay. Never been straight.
知道我還有什麼沒做過嗎
Know what else I've never been?
- 操女人 - 休會
- Inside a woman. - Meeting adjourned.
- 大家都出去 - 你妹的
- Everybody out. - Son of a bitch.
快走 快點 快點 快出去
Come on. Hurry it up. Hurry it up. Come on.
回見 拜拜 到此結束
See you later. Bye-bye. That's it.
朱莉亞 你真的是上癮了
Okay, Julia, you are letting the addiction win.
滾你媽的蛋 羅茲 反正沒人會上你
Oh, fuck you, Roz. No one likes you anyway.
好吧
Okay.
- 準備盡情的來一炮吧 - 來吧
- Let's get you prepped for a fill-n-drill. - Let's do it.
有沒有在牙醫的椅子上做過
Ever done it in a dentist's chair?
我早就想把我的牙醫脫得精光了
I always wanted to nail my dentist.
- 他是個男的 - 我會讓你把他拋到九霄雲外
- He's a man. - I'll make you forget all about him.
你為什麼不先去把椅子準備好呢
Why don't you go get the chair ready?
我要去上個廁所 馬上就回來
I'm gonna visit the men's room real quick.
你可以尿在我身上
Oh, you can do that on me.
嗯 這個
Oh. Well, it's a...
嗯?
And...?
第一次和拉拉來一炮
Well, first time on the slopes,
我可不想尿在美人身上
so I'm gonna stay off the black diamond.
隨你便
Either way.
你們動靜太大了 快走
You guys are so noisy. Let's go.
對不起 對不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
恭喜 我為你出櫃感到驕傲
Congrats. I'm so proud of you for coming out.
- 我不是同性戀 我一會兒就出來 行嗎 - 等等
- I'm not gay. I'll be right out, okay? - Come on.
我覺得我現在走的話肯定會被懷疑
I think it'll be a little suspicious if I disappear.
我給你們掩護到底
Gonna complete the diversion.
- 我們必須走 - 你可是同性戀
- We gotta go. - Thought you were gay.
我不是同性戀 快走 快走 我一會兒就出來
I'm not gay. Go on, go on. I'll be right out.
我懂了 你男女通吃
Oh. I get it. You're bi.
我不是
I'm not bi.
不是?
Not bi?
- 都有沒有一個S 我需要一個S - 有S
- Do you have, an S? I need an S. - S, yes.
- 這個怎麼樣? - 能不能給我一個更嚇人的S
- How's that? - Do you have a scarier S than that?
好的 嗯 這裡
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, here.
這個是從一篇寫新娘酷斯拉的文章上剪下來的
This is from an article about bridezillas.
好的 這個行 好吧 我可以把我拼的讀給你聽嗎
Yeah, that'll do it. Okay, can I read you what I got right now?
- 當然可以 - 好的
- Yeah. Yeah, sure. - Okay.
給我們五十萬
"Give us the $500,000..
不然就殺了這個小孩男兒
...or the little boy dies.
你只剩二十四小時的時間
You have 24 hours."
要是你讀給他聽就好了 這聲音聽起來很嚇人
I wish you were there to read it. Sounds scary in that voice.
這就是我要把信弄得恐怖一點的原因
That's why I wanted scary letters.
這樣他在讀信的時候就像是親耳聽到這聲音一樣
Hopefully he's hearing a voice like that when he reads.
但是 為什麼用"小男孩"兒這個詞
But why "little boy"?
聽起來像是六歲小孩
Makes him sound 6.
那換成"不然就殺了這個成年淫"
Don't wanna be like, "Or the grown man dies."
- 不錯 可以 - 還是有點
- You're right. No, absolutely. - It's not even...
行 給我固體膠 我要把它們黏上
All right, glue stick, and I'm gonna lock this in.
嗯 好的
Oh, great, yeah.
- 把初稿當最終稿 好不好 - 覺得怎麼樣 幹得不錯
- First draft, final draft, right? - How about that? Nice job.
我給你說
God, I tell you what.
不是我自吹自擂
I hope this doesn't sound cocky.
我覺得我們真的是幹這個的料
I think we're really good at this.
絕對地天賦異稟
We're extremely good at it.
我什麼都不說了 這方法比謀殺好多了
I didn't wanna say anything, but way better than murder.
- 比謀殺好得太多了 - 我覺得我們開竅了
- A lot better than murder. - We found our groove.
- 這很搞笑 - 的確有點搞笑
- This is fun. - It is kind of fun.
沒有人會受傷害
Nobody gets hurt.
我早就想弄一封勒索信了
I always wanted to make a ransom note.
人都齊了 走吧
All here. Let's go.
你大爺的 早知道我剛才就把這些都黏貼好了
Son of a bitch. I knew I should've been gluing them as I went along.
嘿 給我說說 感覺怎麼樣
Hey. Hey. Talk to me. How was it?
這種感覺前所未有
It was like something I've just never encountered.
未有什麼 女人?
What, a woman?
我是說她很奔放 而且身體功夫了得
I mean, she's so free. She's so eloquent with her body.
我意思是所有的性能量
I mean, all of that sexual energy...
從她溫柔的胴體的深處流出來
it flows from this place of deep tenderness, you know?
- 那叫陰道 - 別這樣用詞 行了 走吧
- It's called her vagina, Nick. - Please don't talk like that. Come on, let's go.
你看你現在還護著她
Listen. He's being so protective.
聽你這語氣你好像愛上她了
You're talking like you fell in love with her.
你愛上她了嗎 尼克
What, are you in love with her, Nick?
沒有 黛爾
No, Dale.
- 你這反應也太慢了吧 - 他是在沉默
- That was a real long pause right there. - That was a moment of silence.
我沒愛上她 這太扯淡了
I'm not in love with her. That's ridiculous.
她給了我一次豐富多彩積極向上的體驗
She gave me a very rich and positive experience.
是嗎 比絞基露營好多了
Oh, yeah? Better than wrestling camp?
老天 這房子高大上
Oh, boy. Nice house.
他終於清醒了
Well, he's doing well.
算他好運
Good for him.
- 好吧 我們來討論一下行動方案 - 深呼吸 直接上
- All right, let's discuss our options. - Breathe, and go.
嘿 等等
Hey, whoa.
你們倆二逼不能把車停在別人房子的正前方
Guys, you can't just park right in front of the guy's house.
你想把一個意識模糊的富家公子在街上拖著走?
You wanna carry an unconscious dude down the street?
他沉得要死 快行動
He's gonna be way too heavy. Let's move.
說得對 說到點子上了
That's a good point. Good point.
等等 你們不能直接從他的正門進入
Wait, whoa. You can't just walk up to the guy's front door.
你能停下嗎
Will you calm down? We have a plan.
我們計劃好了的 我們計劃好了的放鬆
We have a plan. Just relax.
真的? 那樣最好 我感覺好多了
Oh, do you? That's great. That makes me feel a lot better.
- 你準備好了嗎? - 我準備好了
- Okay, you ready? - Yeah, I'm ready.
看好了 行動
Watch this. Go.
- 我靠 - 我靠
- Fuck. - Fuck.
- 計劃失敗 - 門鎖上了
- It's a bust. - It's locked.
這個計劃沒有考慮門被鎖上的情況?
The plan did not account for a locked door?
鎖上與打開的機率各占百分之五十
Fifty-fifty chance it's gonna be open.
- 你們怎麼算出來的? - 只有鎖上和未鎖兩種情況
- How do you figure that? - Either locked or unlocked.
五十比五十
Fifty-fifty, yeah.
這是基本的數學問題 你今晚怎麼了
It's basic math. What's up with you tonight?
- 把你的信用卡給我 - 好想法
- Give me your credit card. - Good.
- B計劃是插信用卡進去? - 快給我
- Plan B's got a credit card in it? - Come on.
- 你的計劃就是渣 - 你的數學才是渣
- Your plan sucks. - Your math sucks.
這就是事實
That's what's going on.
- 等等 要是他在裡面怎麼辦啊 - 對啊
- Wait. What if he's in there? - Oh, yeah.
- 我們怎麼才能確定 - 為什麼不按門鈴
- How do we make sure? - Why don't you ring the doorbell?
- 我喜歡聰明人的想法 - 別 庫爾特
- I love it. Smart. - Don't. Kurt.
尼瑪 你在耍我吧
Oh, shit. Are you kidding?
- 這麼晚了沒人在裡面的 - 別再按了
- It's dark. Don't think anybody's here. - Don't hit it again.
- 你聽見沒 - 我知道那首歌
- You hear that? - I know that song.
- 那是什麼 - 這是一首歌對吧 難道是
- What is that? - It's a song, right? Is it:
不管你做了什麼
No matter what you do
別 別
No, no.
我都會永遠和你在一起
I will always be with you
- 這歌誰唱的 - 壞手指樂隊
- Who sings that? - Badfinger.
無論你做了什麼 姑娘
Doesn't matter what you do, girl
小聲點
Quiet.
噢 姑娘 和你在一起
Ooh, girl, with you
你們唱對了
You nailed it.
推倒了那陳舊的灰牆
Knock down the old gray wall
他媽的給我閉嘴
Shut the fuck up.
- 嘿 你在大吼大叫 - 你在大吼大叫
- Hey, you're yelling. - You're yelling.
幫幫我 趕緊的
Do me a favor. Hurry up.
沒能打開前門
Fail to open up the front door
所以我們他媽的都趕快離開這裡
so we can get the fuck out of here.
臥槽
Fuck.
- 你操什麼 什麼情況 - 我們有麻煩了
- What's "fuck"? What happened? - We got a problem.
- 沒錯 你看吧 那裡 - 你大爺的
- Yeah, see? Right there? - Goddamn it.
- 就在那裡憂鬱地望著我們 - 那現在怎麼辦
- There it is. Staring back at us. - Okay, what now?
我覺得我們應該聽你的離開這裡
I guess we follow your idea and we get out of here.
- 沒錯 我們必須離開 - 不 嘿 我信用卡還在那裡
- Yeah, we gotta go. - No. Hey. My credit card's in there.
打電話掛失
Call them and cancel.
他們今晚就會送張新的給你
They'll send you a new one overnight.
要是他們發現了這張卡 他們就會知道我們來過這裡
When they find the card, they'll know we were here.
道理就這麼簡單
It's pretty simple.
- 真他媽見鬼 - 他們會知道你來過這裡的
- Oh, shit. - They're gonna know you were here.
快跑 快跑 車 有車
Go, go. Car. Car.
- 你來這裡都做了什麼 - 手指擋住
- What do you got going there? - Finger-flage.
那是他老婆嗎
Is that his wife?
不 那是輛93年的本田思域 她提的是乾洗的衣服
No, that's a '93 Civic and she's carrying dry cleaning.
我猜她是個傭人
I'm gonna go with a maid.
他和他的女傭結婚了?
He married his maid?
雷克斯先生 你在家嗎
Mr. Rex, are you home?
是我 金姆·宋
It me, Kim Song.
我把你乾洗的衣服拿來了
I pick up your dry cleaning.
- 我成功了 - 哇
- Okay, I got it. - Wow.
他品味不錯啊
He's got good taste.
你妹的 都踩彎了
It's bent, goddamn it.
- 很好 清晰的流線 淡雅的顏色 - 快走
- Nice, clean lines, little pops of color. - Let's go.
- 走? - 什麼
- Go? - What?
我們剛進來 再待會
We just got inside. Let's stay.
她也會待在這裡 快他媽出去
So did she. Let's get the fuck out of here.
你放棄了我們的計劃?
Are you quitting on the plan?
- 進去 進去 他回來了 - 為什麼 誰回來了
- Back in. Back in. He's here. - Why? Who's here?
- 雷克斯先生 - 坑爹
- Mr. Rex. - Oh, shit.
金姆 你在?
Kim? You here?
金姆 你幫我拿了襯衫?
Kim, you grab my shirts?
- 是的 雷克斯先生 我現在就去掛起來 - 很好
- Yes, Mr. Rex. I go hang up now. - Great.
等等 等等 金姆 金大小姐
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Kim. Kimbo.
看看這個 告訴我你看到了什麼
Take a look at this. Tell me what you see.
你打算把這些髒東西留在碗槽下面?
Are you gonna leave this mess in the bottom of my sink?
這水?
The water?
對 碗槽底面全是小水滴
Yes, the little water droplets all over the bottom of my sink.
我不知道你是在哪座茅草屋裡長大的
I don't know what thatched hut you grew up in,
但這很噁心
but this is disgusting.
但這只是水而已
But it just water.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
那麼你被炒了
Then you just fire.
你失業了 對你有點殘酷
You lose your job. Too bad for you.
再見
Bye-bye.
看看你自己 我又把你騙了
Look at you. I got you again.
看看這張小籠包一樣的臉
Look at that little chubby face.
你覺得我會在你生日這天把你解僱了?
You think I was gonna fire you on your fucking birthday?
你瘋了嗎 宮城小姐 來 過來
Are you out of your mind, Mrs. Miyagi? Get over here.
你過來 生日快樂
Come here, you. Happy birthday.
我有東西要給你
I got you something.
這可不是地攤貨
That's a good one.
絕對的精品 就好比汽車中的凱迪拉克
That's top of the line. That's like the Cadillac of plungers.
但是只能在這裡用 知道嗎
That's just for here, though, okay?
- 不能帶回家 - 嗯
- No taking it home. - No.
我是 什麼事 哥們
Yeah, what's up, man?
不 我一點都不忙 我正在給我的女傭慶生
Yeah, no, I'm not busy at all. I'm just making my maid's day.
她今天生日
It's her birthday.
嘿 金姆 不過說真的
Hey, Kim, seriously, though.
從今天起能把碗槽擦乾嗎
Can we keep a dry sink from here on in?
是 雷克斯先生
Yes, Mr. Rex.
接著說
What's up?
不 你他媽少來
No, fuck that, man.
金姆
Kim.
伙伴 我在想辦法
Dude, I'm trying.
我爸現在是隻一毛不拔的鐵公雞
My dad is being a total dick about the money.
她在幹什麼
What's she doing?
- 哇靠 我靠 - 她在做什麼
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God. - What is she doing?
- 庫爾特 庫爾特 庫爾特 - 什麼 什麼 什麼
- Kurt. Kurt. Kurt. - What? What? What?
我去 那是我的專利啊 她在做我做的事情
Oh, shit. That's my thing. She's doing my thing.
我真他媽不敢相信她在幹這事
I can't believe she's fucking doing that.
她插得還不夠深
She's not going in deep enough.
- 你覺得她是在洗菊花嗎? - 顯然是個新手
- Do you think she's just cleaning? - What a rookie.
她走了 好吧 好吧
Okay, there she goes. Okay. All right.
泡菜小姐
Kimchi.
- 他來了 - 看到了
- There he is. - Okay.
- 不 他要刷牙了 - 要刷了
- Oh, no. He's gonna brush his teeth. - He is.
- 他要刷了 - 他開始刷了
- He's gonna do it. - Here he goes.
- 刷 - 刷
- Do it. - Do it.
耶 耶 耶 耶 耶 耶 耶
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
你這二逼 好好地刷一刷
Yeah, get them nice and clean, you son of a bitch.
真過癮
So satisfying.
等等 哥兒幾個 現在呢我們在做什麼
Wait, guys. Okay. Now what, though?
我們現在在做什麼
What are we doing? What do we do now?
等他上床睡覺 黛爾打開氣瓶
We wait for him to go to bed. Dale starts the gas.
我把勒索信準備好
I've got the ransom note.
- 不是現在 - 他說了 黛爾打開氣瓶
- Not now. - He said, "Dale, start the gas."
我是說了 黛爾打開氣瓶
I said, "Dale starts the gas."
後面在打開 二貨 關掉
Later, you idiot. Turn that off.
不能把氣體放在這裡
We can't have the gas in here.
我會把這信放在
Okay. I'll put this on the...
- 關掉 - 我在關 這壞了還是怎麼了
- Turn it off. - I'm trying to. It's broken or something.
你開玩笑吧 把它扳到另一邊
Are you kidding me? Turn it the other way.
我關了一百萬次
We dropped it like a million times.
我覺得我們把它弄壞了 看見了嗎
I think we broke it. No, see?
- 一點都不起作用了 - 我們快出去
- It's not doing anything. - Let's get out.
從這裡出去? 你在說些什麼! 他就在外面
Get outa here? What are you talking about? He's right outside.
我去 - 他就在外面
Shit. - He's out there.
快把這罐子拿出去
Then get the can out of here.
老兄
Dude.
別笑了 這有什麼好笑的?
Don't start laughing. What is funny about this?
看看你的臉 快看看他的臉
Look at your face. Look at his face.
- 不好 - 老兄 你的臉...
- Oh, no. - Dude, your face...
是笑氣 你們笑是不是因為笑氣?
The gas. Is this the gas?
不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
聽著 我們得振作起來
Hey. Listen. Keep it together.
是的 就是因為笑氣
Yes, it's the gas.
- 這感覺真好 - 你才要振作呢
- It's pretty good. - You keep it together.
我想打的是他
I was trying to hit him.
- 你們兩個 - 他要倒了
- Guys. - No, no, no.
好了 我沒事 我沒事 我們應該...
Okay. I'm good. I'm good. Let's...
糟糕 庫爾特 庫爾特 你的手機
Shit. Kurt. Kurt, your phone.
你的手機響了 快接電話
Your phone. Answer your phone.
- 好的 好的 - 我們在哪裡呢?
- I got it. I got it. I got it. - Where are we?
- 快把你的手機關掉 - 為什麼你老婆打我電話?
- Shut it off. - Why is your wife calling me?
我的天啊 我昨天晚上沒回家 她大概嚇壞了
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. She's probably freaking out. I didn't come home last night.
安靜一點
Quiet.
老兄 把你的頭從我的褲襠移開
Dude, get your fucking head out of my crotch.
你們看看這白天的景致!
Will you look at this fucking view during the daytime?
這一定是在開玩笑!
You kidding me?
- 他好像走了 - 難以置信
- He seems gone. - Unbelievable.
-床已經鋪好了 - 我完全無法相信這一切
- Bed's made. - I can't believe this.
我們應該確認一下他...
We should maybe just check...
- 雷克斯! - 嘿
- Hey! Rex! - Hey.
雷克斯! 雷克斯!
Rex! Rex!
黛爾
Dale.
要是他還在家怎麼辦?
Did you have a plan if he responded?
我沒想那麼長遠
I didn't think that far ahead.
要是我的話就不會回應
I would've just been quiet.
就是啊
Yeah.
我發現早上的你更笨
You get even dumber in the mornings.
- 你在擔心什麼? -  我們快走吧
- What are you worried about? - Let's go.
- 他有一半的機率在家 - 對啊
- Fifty-fifty chance, you know, fifty-fifty chance he was here. - Yeah.
我回去之後史黛西肯定氣翻了
You know, Stacy's just gonna completely flip out when I get home.
她肯定會說: "什麼樣的爸爸是不回家的? "
What kind of dad doesn't come home?
你給我閉嘴 求你了
Shut that down. Okay?
如果現在最壞的結果
If the worst thing that happens
只是你的家庭問題...
from this clusterfuck is your domestic problems...
那我們還算走運的 我們剛剛逃過一劫
we can consider ourselves lucky. We just dodged a huge bullet back there.
我們差點做了一個一生中最傻的決定
We almost made the worst decision of our lives.
那倒是真的 你知道為什麼嗎?
That's true. You know why?
如果他打開了衣櫥然後看到了我們
Cause if he opens that closet door and sees us,
我們現在就在監獄裡了
we're in prison right now.
是是是 所以我們非常 非常地幸運
That's right. So we're very, very lucky.
我們之前是不是腦抽了?
What the fuck is the matter with us?
我告訴你們
You know what? I tell you what.
要是有一點點事情是按我們計劃發展的 我們肯定就成功了
If a couple tiny things went our way, we could've pulled that off.
不 我們不是罪犯 我們一點都不會犯罪
No. We're not criminals. We suck at crime.
我們都是善良的正常人
We're like nice, normal guys.
- 我喜歡棒球 我每天都穿褲子 - 是
- I like baseball. I wear pants. - Yup.
- 我們又得回去替人打工 - 辛勤工作啊 兄弟
- Back to being cogs in the machine. - Cogs. Cogs, dude.
辛勤工作也沒什麼不好
Cogs are good.
我反倒覺得輕鬆一些了
It's a relief, you know?
就像很重的東西...
It's like a weight lifted off your...
是啊 從肩上卸下來
That's right, my shoulder.
我們要重新開始...
It's a fresh start where everything's...
我過會打電話給你們
I'll call you guys later.
- 求你們別殺我 - 我去!
- Please don't kill me. - Fuck!
- 哇靠 - 這是怎麼回事?
- Oh, fuck. - What the fuck is that?
怎麼會這樣? 我們都做了什麼?
What the fuck is that? What did we do?
難道我們吸足了笑氣還能把他綁架了?
We kidnapped him while we're high on nitrous?
然後還能自己回到衣櫥裡睡覺?
Then what? We just went back into the closet and went to sleep?
- 我們為什麼要這麼做? - 噓 噓 - 怎麼了?
- Why would we do that? - Shh... shh... shh - What?
他是在哭嗎?
Is he crying?
噢 我的天啊 太好笑了
Oh, my God. The best.
真是太好笑了
That was so good.
快把我拉出來
Help me out.
你們的表情... 看看你們的表情
The look on your... Look at this.
我實在忍不住了... 你們嚇傻了吧
I really couldn't... Your fucking face.
- 我的天 - 嗨
- Oh, my God. - Hey, man. Yeah. Whoo-whee.
你真騙到我們了
You had us.
- 發生了什麼? - 我也不知道
- What's happening? - I don't know.
- 到底怎麼回事? - 噢天啊
- What's happening? - Oh, boy.
天啊 謝謝你們
Oh, my God, you guys. Thank you.
我很長時間沒笑得這麼開心了
I have not laughed like that in a long time.
真是太好笑了 這個笑話簡直是精神食糧
Oh, my God. Goddamn, that was great. Food for the soul.
不錯 我們就是為了搞笑的
Good, well, we were just trying to be funny.
- 沒有傷害 就不算犯規 對吧 - 是啊是啊
- You know, no harm, no foul, right? - Yeah, yeah.
我真的完全低估你們了
Guys, I completely underestimated you.
你們還真有些本事 你們還真是令人印象深刻
You fuckers have some low-hanging balls. I mean it. I'm impressed.
我起床之後就發現你們在我的衣櫥裡...
I mean, I wake up, I find you three in my closet...
還有一張勒索信和一個裝笑氣的破罐子
along with a ransom note, a big old bottle of nitrous.
我就在想 "媽蛋 這幾個混蛋是想要給我聞笑氣迷昏我"
I'm like, "Holy shit. These fuckers were gonna gas me."
我差點就報警了 不過我又想 "等一下
I'm about to call the cops when I think, "Hold up a sec.
這幾個人可能有什麼陰謀"
These guys may be onto something."
我想加入你們
I wanna partner up on this thing.
什麼陰謀? 你在講些什麼?
What thing? What are you talking about?
我聽不太懂
I'm not sure what you mean.
- 就是這個陰謀啊 綁架我啊 - 這
- This thing. My kidnapping. - Oh.
說實話 我和我爸...
Truth be told, Pop and I...
我們之間出現了一些問題
we've hit a rough patch.
他不替我付帳了
He's refusing to cover some of my expenses.
說來話長 總之 你們選的時間點不能再合適了
Long story. Anyway, your timing could not have been better.
這是一條槍魚嗎?
Is this a fucking marlin?
雷克斯 你的提議不錯 不過我們已經決定收手不幹了
Rex, this is, cool and all, but we decided, like, we're out.
- 我們不會犯罪的 - 這不是我們該幹的
- We're not doing crime. - Not our thing.
他說的對 其實我們不打算綁架你了
Yeah, no, he's right. No, the kidnapping is off, actually.
- 不 不 你們還得繼續下去 - 不 我們不幹了
- No, no, no, it's on. - No, it's off.
不是的 你們必須得繼續"綁架"我 我已經把勒索信寄給我爸了
No, it's totally on. I sent the ransom note to my dad.
- 你什麼? - 你做了什麼?
- You what? - You did what?
勒索信寫得太好了
And it was brilliant.
誰想出要把我寫成一個小男孩的?
Who came up with that thing about me being a little boy?
- 幹得漂亮 - 謝謝
- Beautiful. - Thanks.
你只要了50萬美元 我還覺得少了呢
I was a little insulted you only asked for $500,000 for me.
我就值那麼些錢?
Is that all I'm worth?
不過也不是很麻煩 我又添了一個零上去
No sweat. I tacked on another zero.
- 五百百萬? - 天 太多了
- Five-hundred million? - Wow, that's a ton.
- 是五百萬 - 五百萬
- Five million, guys. - Five million.
- 五百萬啊 - 對
- Five million. - Five. Right.
是的 五百萬 分你們一百萬 分我四百萬
Yeah, 5 million. One million dollars for you guys, and 4 for me.
我們不如去搞一個付費電話來打勒索電話?
Why don't we get a payphone to make that ransom call?
呃 雷克斯 還是算了吧
Yeah, Rex, let's not.
我們感謝你慷慨的提議
We appreciate the generous offer,
也很感謝你沒有報警 不過還是算了吧
and thank you very much for not calling the cops, but we're gonna pass.
- 別這樣 - 就是這樣
- No. - Yeah.
伙伴們 這難道不是個天大的好消息嗎?
Guys. Guys, how is this anything but great news?
你們只要完成計劃
All I'm asking you to do is finish your own plan
就能拿到雙倍的錢了
but for double the money.
而且我是你們的內線
Plus, it got a thousand times easier
所以完成這個計劃比原來容易多了
because now I'm your inside man.
我可以確保我爸付贖金
I can make sure Dad pays up.
然後等你們"放了我"之後
And then when you, "set me free"...
我就告訴警察是另外三個白痴綁架了我
I tell the cops it was three other morons that went that way.
哇塞 這倒不是個壞主意
Oh. Wow. That's not the worst idea I've ever heard.
-這比我們原來的計劃好 - 好多了
- It's better than our original idea. - A lot better.
等我們一下
Give us one second.
你們在想點什麼?
Fucking what?
- 我們根本不能相信他 - 你當然可以相信我了
- We can't trust this guy. - You can trust me.
你說得對 他們已經騙過我們一次了
No, you're right. They burned us once already.
我們不能再被騙了
We're not gonna get burned again.
- 得了吧 - 謝謝你 不過還是算了
- Nice try. - Thanks but no thanks.
- 我們三個都不同意 - 都不同意
- That's a Nick-Kurt-Dale no from us. - Nick, Kurt and Dale.
- 所以 謝了 不過再見了 - 嗯
- So, thank you, but adios. - Yeah.
- 好吧 - 你要我們送你回去嗎?
- Okay. - You need a ride?
不用了 那我還是在這裡多待一會
No. I think I'll hang out here.
逃出你們的魔掌...
You know, escape from your clutches...
然後報警
and call the police.
那你報警呀 我們又沒有綁架過你
Go ahead. Call them. We never kidnapped you.
- 不 你們綁架了 - 我們才沒有
- Yeah, you did. - We didn't.
- 你們的確把我拐走了 - 明明就沒有
- Yeah, you abducted me. - We did not.
可你們把我帶來這裡啦
Yeah, you brought me back here.
- 我們打鬥了一番 - 真是糟糕 你可不能這樣
- There was a struggle. - Oh, shit. Come on, man.
有東西被打破了
Things got broken.
怎麼會... ?
What the...?
然後 你們就打了我
And then, you assaulted me.
- 天啊 - 什麼?
- Oh, shit. - What?
這人一定是瘋了
This guy's fucking nuts.
雷克斯 計劃早就結束了
Hey, Rex? It's off, pal.
然後你們又無情地揍了我一頓
Oh, and then you beat me. Mercilessly.
天啊 他在自己打自己
Holy shit. He's Fight Clubbing himself. We got a Fight Clubber.
之後我就到這裡來 找到了這個電話
And then I found my way up here and I found this phone.
- 我就撿起聽筒... - 不
- I picked up the receiver... - Oh, no.
... 然後我就撥了九...
...and I dialed 9...
- 別別別 - 拜託 玩笑已經開過了
- Don't, don't, don't. - Come on. Joke's over.
- ... 一... - 你不能再按一了
- ...1... - Don't you hit the second 1.
- 快停下 - 別按了
- Don't do it. - Don't hit it.
我不知道要去哪裡
I don't know where I'm going.
我也不知道在哪裡能找到付費電話
I don't know where you find pay phones.
- 這個公園裡有付費電話 - 好吧
- There's some pay phones at the park here. - Okay.
我們要幹這一票了 冒險已經開始了 你們是不是都很激動啊?
Boys, we are doing this. The adventure begins. Who's fired up?
你們都太消極了 搞得我很不好受 拜託了
Such a negative energy. This is killing me. Guys, come on.
- 你能不能移過去一點? - 不行 我就是坐在中間的
- Can you scoot over just a smidge? - No, I sit in the middle.
- 那是他的座位 - 一直是這樣的 雷克斯
- That's his seat. - It's a whole thing, Rex.
我知道 只是你擠著我了
I know. Just you're crowding me.
我怎麼擠著他了?
I'm crowding this guy now?
他逼著我們綁架他 我還擠到他了? 這太荒謬了
He's forcing us to kidnap him, and I'm crowding him?
哇 哇 哇 兄弟 冷靜一下
Whoa, whoa, whoa, buddy. Simmer down.
綁架是你想出來的 記得不?
Kidnapping was your idea, remember?
- 但之後我們放棄了 - 對啊 就是這樣
- But then we had the idea to not do it. - Yeah, exactly.
- 我就是坐在中間的! - 嘿 嘿
- I sit in the middle! - Hey, hey.
- 黛爾 你就按他說的做吧 - 我的天啊
- Dale, just do what he says. - For chrissake.
啊 這樣不錯
Oh, God. That is nice.
舒服多了
This is way better.
這就是在胡扯
This is bullshit, by the way.
不好意思 哈里斯醫生
Excuse me, Dr. Harris.
昨天晚上有人在辦公室嗎?
Was someone in the office last night?
昨天晚上八點我的性癮交流協會在這裡聚會
My sex-addiction group met here at 8.
對的 不過電腦記錄到之前有人進來過
Oh. Yes. But, doctor, the keypad logged an earlier entrance.
真的嗎?
Really?
那我們看一下新裝的監控
Let's check our fancy new camera system.
那是個同性戀 真是奇怪
That's a gay guy. It's so weird.
他看起來不太像同性戀
He didn't bone me like a gay guy.
他就是流了點眼淚
He only cried, like, a little bit.
而且他對於他的肛門很拘謹 這很奇怪
And he was oddly squeamish about his own asshole, which is weird.
- 這太奇怪了 - 我也是這麼想的
- It's so weird. - Yeah, that's what I thought.
那是黛爾嗎?
Is that Dale?
他和庫爾特和布萊斯頓在一塊兒幹什麼?
What's he doing with Kurt and Blanston?
- 我們要報警嗎? -  不用了
- Should we call the police? - No.
還是不了
No.
我來解決他們
I'll take care of them.
好好享受吧
Enjoy.
這還是蠻不錯的 學著點
It's good stuff. Learn something.
好了 已經撥出去了
All right, it's ringing.
記住 籌碼都在你們這裡
Remember, you guys hold all the cards.
嚴肅一些 你們會做的很好的
Game faces. You are going to crush this.
等一下 他知道我們的聲音 我們應該裝出一些口音
Hold on. He knows what we sound like. We gotta use an accent.
- 不要裝口音 那太奇葩了 - 好主意 庫爾特
- No accents. That's ridiculous. - That's a great idea, Kurty.
比爾德·斯特姆公司
Boulder Stream.
- 那是誰? 是秘書嗎? - 裝出口音來
- Who is this? The secretary? - Accent. Yeah.
親愛的 讓我和伯特·漢森先生通電話
Hey, homey. Let me speak to Mr. Bert Hanson.
不 我不介意等一會
No, I don't mind holding.
我費了好大勁才打通你的電話
I just barely even called you right now already.
- 這太種族歧視了 - 太種族歧視了
- That's incredibly racist. - Super racist.
還是用一個南方口音吧
Just do a Southern accent.
南方? 我會南方口音 沒問題
Southern? Southern I got. Southern. No problem.
漢森
Hanson.
你好啊 伙伴
Well, howdy there, partner.
你家公子現在在我們手上
This here's the gents what got your young'un and all.
我們需要談一談
And, well, we got some talking to do and...
我讓你裝南方口音 而不是老礦工的口音
Southern, not old prospector.
我覺得剛剛那還不錯
I thought that was pretty good.
聽著 你們這些卑賤的老工人
Listen, you lowlife bottom-feeder,
我沒時間和你們瞎鬧
I don't have time for this little fuck-around.
要麼你現在掛掉電話
Either this ends right now,
要麼我就給你吃子彈
or it ends with bullets in your skulls.
不 你閉嘴 你一點都嚇不倒我們 你兒子在我們這裡
Now, you hush. You don't scare us one bit. We got your boy.
這肯定把你嚇壞了
I bet that tears you up something fierce.
我怎麼知道我兒子真在你那裡?
How do I know you really have my boy?
爸
Dad.
爸 是不是你 求求你快來救我 他們太變態了
Dad, is that you? Please. They're crazy.
他們跟我說 要是你報警的話就殺了我
They told me if you call the police, they'd kill me.
求求你按他們說的做 爸 我不想死
Please. Please, do whatever they say. I don't wanna die, Dad.
別報警
No police.
- 我的天 - 雷克斯? 雷克斯? 你在哪裡?
- God! - Rex? Rex? Where are you?
你給我聽好了 你必須把
Now, you listen. Y'all gonna have to rassle up...
五百萬現金交給我們
that 5 million bucks in cash.
全都是100塊的紙幣
We're looking at all 100s.
- 不許做記號 - 不許做記號
- Unmarked. - Unmarked.
- 不能有跟蹤器 – 不許帶跟蹤器 也不許在錢上面做標記
- No tracers. - No tracers and no dye packs neither.
不然的話 我們就...
Otherwise, we gonna take your boy...
用我們有的
and string him up by his pretty little neck...
最粗的繩子
with the roughest, coarsest piece of rope we got...
綁在他纖細的小脖子上
in our rope inventory.
聽明白了? 二十四小時之內不交錢我們就撕票
You understand? You got 24 hours before he dead.
- 太棒了 - 我們做到了
- Yes. - That is how it's done.
我們走吧
Let's go. All right.
剛剛簡直太棒了
Guys, that was great.
真是有意思
That was so much fun.
- 絕對的 - 你們太厲害了
- Absolutely. - You were incredible.
- 謝謝你替我們買了零食 - 應該的
- Thanks for getting us snacks, dude. - You earned it.
所以現在我們做些什麼?
So now what? What do we do?
- 好的 - 接下來的計劃是什麼?
- Okay. - What's the plan?
我們不如回辦公室吧
I say we go back to the office.
好嗎? 先低調一些
Okay? Lay low for a little while.
- 然後我們就等著拿錢了
And we wait for that money train to roll in.
把音響開響點 我喜歡這首歌
Oh! Turn up this song. I love this one.
我們就要完成綁架計劃了
We're doing this thing.
我不喜歡打破你們歡樂的心情
I hate to break up the car party,
不過 雷克斯 你根本就沒有想好交換贖金的計劃
but, Rex, you don't have a plan for the ransom drop...
綁架犯最容易在那時候被抓住
and that is the part where people get caught.
沒有警察 交贖金就很容易了
Wow. The ransom drop is only hard if the police are involved.
是啊 可是萬一他報警了怎麼辦?
Yeah. But what if he does call the police?
那就不妙了
Because that wouldn't be good.
他是億萬富翁 他不會為了五百萬就不管我死活了
He's a billionaire. He's not gonna risk my life over $5 million.
有了庫爾特的精彩表演
After Kurt's little performance,
他不可能報警的
there's no way he's gonna call the cops.
我的表演很精彩? 那你呢? 你演得太好了
My performance? What about yours? You were so in the moment.
- 你真這麼覺得? - 你演得很好! 另外你也…
- You think so? - You were great! And you were…
你們都閉嘴吧
Get your mouths off his dick, okay?
- 每個人都演得很好 – 冷靜一下
- Everyone was doing pretty good. - Whoa. Take it down a notch.
等一下 都別說話 史黛西打電話來了
Wait. Shut up, shut up, shut up. This is Stacy.
噢 我的天啊 我忘記打給她了 嗨 親愛的
Oh, my God. I forgot to call her. Hi, honey.
- 你昨天晚上去哪了? - 是這樣的
- Where have you been all night? - Here's what happened.
我在公司睡著了 然後...
I fell asleep at the office, and...
真的嗎? 我的手機定位軟體說你並不在公司
Really? Because Find My iPhone said you weren't at the office.
黛爾你是不是有小三了?
What, are you cheating on me, Dale?
- 聽著 你現在心情不好... - 糟糕
- Look, you're upset and... - Oh, shit.
- 該死的 - 他報警了
- Oh, God. Goddamn it. - He called the cops.
- 我們被抓現行了 - 被抓? 我的天啊
- Oh, we're busted. - Busted? Oh, my God.
- 不是我被捕 - 快開車
- I'm not busted. - Drive.
沒有人被捕
No one is busted in a bad sense of the word.
太晚了 盧佩已經看到我們了 開過去
Too late. Lupe's got us. Pull in.
把你的頭放到我大腿上
Put your head in my lap.
親愛的 沒有人的頭在我的大腿上
Honey, no one's head's going in my lap.
這只是一句流行語罷了 我不能和你多講了
It's something guys are saying now. I can't talk.
- 躲起來 躲起來 - 我完蛋了
- Hide, hide, hide. - I am fucked.
- 我們走進去就行了 冷靜一點 - 靠
- Let's just go in. Be calm and be cool. - Shit.
- 嗨 - 你們好
- Hi. - Gentlemen.
- 這房子是你們的嗎? - 這個地方?
- You own this establishment? - This place here?
我不知道 我這輩子就沒什麼東西是我自己的
I don't know. Do you really own anything in this lifetime?
我們只是租的
We're currently renting.
我們就租了這些東西 電啊 質子啊
It's all just material. Electrons, protons.
- 對的 - 嚴格來說
- Yeah. We do. - Technically.
我要問你們一下 你們的公司最近和伯特·漢森有商業往來嗎?
Let me ask you, has your company done business recently with a Mr. Bert Hanson?
- 巴布爾·范松? 沒聽說過 - 的確沒有
- Barb Fanson? Doesn't ring a bell. - Not really ringing a bell.
- 我也覺得沒聽說過 - 我們不認識他
- I don't think that we have. - Not our guy.
那還真是有意思 據我所知 你們正和他合作
That's interesting. The way I hear it, you're working with him.
事情對你們很不利
And things didn't shake out too well for you boys.
- 噢 伯特 - 噢 伯特·漢森
- Oh, Bert. - Oh. Bert Hanson.
- 沒錯 - 他是那麼說的嗎?
- Yeah. - Is that what he said?
- 伯特·漢森? 是的 我們認識他 - 那老頭
- Bert Hanson? Oh, yeah. We know him. - That guy.
我們有利益衝突
We had a business disagreement.
- 很大 - 沒什麼大不了
- Big whoop. - No big deal.
- 事情都過去了 - 我們對那傢伙超級友好
- Water under the bridge. - We're super friendly with the guy.
你們真寬容
You're very forgiving.
因為幾乎所有我談話的都認為他是混球
Because almost everyone I've talked to thinks he's an asshole.
- 他們是那樣認為的? - 我可以理解
- Do they think that? - I could see that.
言辭激烈 我不知道是否會那麼說
Strong word. I don't know if I'd use it.
我們喜歡他 當然他兒子不該被綁架
We like the guy. Definitely don't think his son deserves to be kidnapped.
綁架?
Kidnapped?
誰提了綁架一事?
Who said anything about kidnapping?
- 我想是你說了 - 我沒有
- I wanna say you did. - I didn't.
- 我聽你說了 - 我沒有
- I heard you say it. - I didn't.
- 我也覺得你說了 - 我確信沒有
- I feel like you did. - I'm sure I did.
你說了"綁架" 我還想"多奇怪的用詞"
You said "kidnapping." I was like, "What a weird word."
- 有點像"綁家" - 不 沒有 我說了嗎?
- Should be more "kidnabbing." - No, I did not. Did I say that?
- 我想可能有吧 長官 - 你確定?
- I think you might have, sir. - You sure?
他們亂吵的時候我走神了 但很確定有
Well, I got a little lost with all their yammering, but pretty sure.
好吧 可能我說了
All right, maybe I did.
- 嗨 - 難熬的一週
- Hey. - It's been a long week.
還會在聯絡
We'll be in touch.
是 隨時
Yeah. Anytime you want.
不要擔心 因為你透露的大事...
Don't worry, because the main thing is that you said it...
別提了 別提了
Stop talking. Stop talking.
你說得夠多了 夠了
You've done plenty, plenty of talking.
你去哪? 回來 過來 我們去這裡
Where you going? Come back here. Come over here. We're going this way.
不用謝我 回家享受天倫之樂吧
I don't want you to thank me. Just go home and enjoy your family.
享受假期吧 伙伴們 你們掙來的
Enjoy the rest of the day off, everyone. You've earned it.
警察來查過了 確保晚上都鎖門了
The police were just checking. Making sure we're locking up at night.
他們維護鄰里安全 他們是英雄
You know, they're keeping the neighborhood safe. They're heroes.
好了 都安頓好了
Okay, all taken care of.
- 沒事 大家都走了 - 不 不 他...
- No, everyone's gone. - No, no, he...
他崩潰了
He's spinning out.
我很清楚我性命攸關
I was really clear my life was in danger.
他卻還是報警了
He called the police anyway.
沒錯 自從他報警...
Yeah, and since he did...
現在很明瞭了我們不能再繼續騙局了...
it's pretty clear that we're not gonna be able to continue with the scam...
五百萬對他來說毛毛雨
Five million dollars is nothing to him.
但我想我還不如那些錢
But I guess it's worth more to him than my life.
- 看在老天分上 我是他兒子 - 噢 天 都成淚人了
- I'm his son, for chrissake. - Oh, boy. We got a crier.
瞧瞧他哭的時候眼睛水汪汪的
Look how blue his eyes get when he's crying.
抱歉 真他媽的尷尬
I'm sorry. This is so fucking embarrassing.
- 噢 沒有 不 不 不 - 沒有
- Oh, no. No, no, no. - No.
給廁紙 你可以擦擦鼻子
Toilet paper here. You can blow your nose.
你父親報警
Just because your dad called the cops
不意味著他不愛你
doesn't mean he doesn't love you.
是的 當然不意味
No, of course not.
哦 天啊 我想這是他的第一反應
Oh, my gosh. I'm sure it was just his first reaction.
- 他嚇壞了 迷惘 - 這是本能 黛爾就是位父親
- He's scared, confused. - It's natural. I mean, Dale's a dad.
我也是當爸爸的
I'm a dad.
你能想像有人搶走其中一個孩子?
Can you imagine if someone stole one of them?
- 無法想像 - 你會報警
- I can't imagine. - You would call the cops.
不 我想不會報警 我承擔不了那風險
No, I don't think I'd call the cops. I couldn't take that risk.
- 不同情況 - 操 抱歉
- Different situation. - Shit, I'm sorry.
壞例子
Bad example.
也許獨處會有用
Maybe some alone time would be helpful.
我們出去 讓他靜靜?
Why don't we step outside, give him a minute?
我們會回來的 不要做傻事
We'll come back, don't do anything rash.
那根松點的繩子 我不希望他...
Get the loose rope. I don't want him to...
我們只能自求多福
We can only hope.
我們去外面談談?
Can I talk to you outside, please?
- 噢 天啊 - 兄弟 我為那傢伙難過
- Oh, boy. - Man, I feel terrible for that guy.
我明白 你在開玩笑? 可憐 可憐的娃
I know. Are you kidding me? Poor, poor guy.
這是很艱難 艱難
I mean, that is rough. Rough.
你們是在拆我台嗎?
Are you guys shitting me in there?
他父親不要他為了... 對於他可能就是無足輕重
His dad sold him out for... It was probably nothing to him.
- 錢於他 - 那傢伙不差錢
- Pennies to him. - The guy's rich.
都撼動我內心了 請有點同情?
That would rock me to my core. Have a little empathy. Please?
知道現在什麼情況嗎? 你心懷怨憤
Know what's going on? You're holding a grudge right now.
是的 就是那樣
Yes, you do that.
- 你做什麼都繃緊 會得癌症的 - 確實
- You get all tight. You're gonna get cancer. - You do.
- 我也不想那樣 - 讓往事隨風而去
- I don't want that. - Let the past be the past.
我們沒有在過去
We're not in the fucking past.
我們是進行中 而你們...
We're in the goddamn present. And you guys...
你們在談什麼? 你們像是患有斯德哥爾摩症
What are you talking about? You're acting like you have Stockholm Syndrome.
斯德哥爾摩症:被劫持人質對劫持者產生好感並同情、寬容他
什麼?
What is that?
- 什麼 像是倒時差? - 不
- What, like jet lag? - No.
- 你們看我累嗎? - 你沒有 沒有
- Do I look tired to you? - You don't. No.
- 你看起來不疲倦 - 我很好
- You don't look tired. - I'm fine.
斯德哥爾摩症發生在你與捕手緊密相連
Stockholm Syndrome's when you bond with your captors.
噢 好了 等等 才是人質
Oh, okay. Well, then hold on a second. He's the hostage.
所以這是反斯德哥爾摩症
So this would be reverse Stockholm Syndrome.
沒錯 我們沒有 好嗎?
Yeah, and we don't have that, okay?
他只是一個非常 非常 非常可愛的傢伙 我很喜歡他
He's just a really, really, really likable guy. I like him a lot.
- 他很招人愛 - 他才是贏家
- He's really likable. - The guy's a winner.
跟著贏的人混才是好的
It's nice to be around a winner.
噢 天 直覺是對的 尼克 算了
Oh, boy. It feels right, Nick. Come on.
我們要做的就是
Here's what we're gonna do.
我們進去 告訴他我們撤出這個計劃....
We're gonna go in, tell him cops were never part of this plan...
以及現在這破事結束了 走
and the shit ends now. Let's do it.
好 但聽聽我們的怨憤
Okay, but hear us out about festering.
你就不能好好談話
Like you can't have a conversation.
這是個好主意 只是沒奏效
It was a wonderful idea. Didn't work out.
所以我們最好回歸正軌...
So I think the best thing to do is just to pull the plug...
然後你去告訴警察那些綁你的人臨陣退縮了...
and you tell the police that the guys who got you chickened out...
放走了你 他們遠走高飛了
let you go, they're long gone.
他們沒有全部臨陣退縮
They didn't all chicken out.
現在不是退出的時候 哥們
Now's not the time to back off, boys.
我說我們砍掉一個腳趾 寄給他要雙倍贖金
I say we chop off a toe, mail it to him and double the ransom.
現在你能說話了 砍 砍 砍
Now you're talking. Chop, chop, chop.
沒錯! 等等 誰的腳趾?
Yes! Wait, whose toe?
- 不是 不是 不是我的 - 誰的都不是
- Not it. Not it. Not my toe. - No one's toe.
收好你的腳趾 該撤了
Keep your toes. Time to call it off.
尼克 尼克 來嘛
Nick. Nick. Come on.
- 尼克 看著我 - 唉
- Nick, look at me. - Oy.
聽著 如果我們現在放棄 我會沒事 對吧?
Look, man, if we give up now, I'll be just fine, you know?
但你們 你的員工 老天
But you guys, your employees, for God's sake.
- 黛爾的小兔崽子 - 女孩們 庫爾特
- Dale's little boys. - Girls, Kurt.
- 嗨 謝謝 是的 - 沒錯 你們都完蛋了
- Hey, thanks. Yes. - Yeah. You're all fucked.
- 尼克 繼續吧 - 繼續吧
- Nick, come on. - Come on.
你陷於囹圄之境唯有死路一條
You can't roll over and die when your back's against the wall.
- 不要自找死路 - 你得謹慎
- Don't roll over and die. - You gotta be careful.
- 你得拿回屬於你的 - 要回!
- You have to take what's yours. - Take it!
報上你名 寫下名字並說 "那是我的"
Put your name on it. Write your name on it and say, "That's mine."
並奪回
And take it.
我想這裡還是由我來主導 好嗎?
I think I'll take it from here, okay?
- 他懂的- 他懂的 他聽著呢
- He's got it. - He's got it. Listen right here.
- 這就是你想要的 - 不是我們
- This is where you want it to come from. - Not us.
- 我知道了! - 抱歉 雷克斯 抱歉
- I got it! - Sorry, Rex. Sorry.
- 他明白 - 得了 哥們
- He's got it. - Come on, man.
幫我也幫你們向我那混蛋老爹復仇
Help me help you get revenge on my asshole dad...
- ... 你們還會有一百萬的回報 - 沒錯
- ...and get you paid a million bucks cash. - Yes.
伙伴們 聽起來棒極了 但沒辦法實現
Boy, it sounds awesome, but there's no way to get it done.
那是不對的這樣如何?
That's not true. How about this?
我們集思廣益如何? 腦力激盪一下
How about if we just put our heads together? We brainstorm a little.
如果我們想不出你喜歡的贖金計劃
If we don't come up with a ransom plan that you love,
我們就撤消
we pull the plug.
- 那時你放我們走? - 我保證
- Then you'd let us walk? - You have my word.
但如果我們想出了振奮人心的...
But if we do come up with something really inspired...
那我們就加入奪金
then we're in it to win it.
好吧 我阻止不了腦力激盪
Well, I can't stop anybody from brainstorming.
你最好了
You're the best.
- 好了 - 樓上見 伙伴們
- All right. - I'll see you upstairs, man.
"陰道"帶G還是J?
Is "vagina" with a G or a J?
好了
All right.
我們從頭到尾理一遍
Let's run it down from the top.
好 首先我們把雷克斯綁在
Okay. First we tie up Rex
第三街區一間被遺棄的倉庫
in one of those abandoned warehouses off 3rd.
然後用一次性手機打給伯特 手機是預付費而且不可追蹤的
Then we call Bert on a dark phone. It's prepaid and untraceable.
到四號街區橋的長椅進行投放
Go to the bench on the 4th Street Bridge to make the drop.
時間很短追蹤不到電話
Not long enough to trace the call.
靠
Goddamn it.
這群傢伙是專業的
These guys are pros.
我要把追蹤器放包裡
I want a tracer put in that bag.
警察把手底下所有人派往橋邊監視
The police are sending everyone they've got to watch the bridge.
整裝待發 全程戒備
Weapons tight. Eyes on.
好吧 戰術指令 紅色小隊
All right, tactical command, red team.
我們到了
Here we go.
但當他到那裡...
But when he gets there...
他找到我預先放置的一次性手機
he finds the dark phone that I planted ahead of time.
然後我們用另一隻一次性手機打給他
Then we call him from the second dark phone,
告訴他去市中心
and tell him to proceed downtown.
你好
Hello.
你要去曼德拉草賓館下的車庫
You'll wanna pull into the garage under the Mandrake Hotel
並停在4421車位
and park in Space 4421.
然後你會找到一個紅包
There, you will find a red bag.
把錢裝入那個包裡 然後開出去等待下一個投放地點
You will transfer the money into this bag, then drive out and await the location of the drop.
然後我們告訴他如果有人跟蹤他
And we tell him if anyone follows him in,
他兒子就沒命了
his son's a fucking corpse.
當伯特開到足夠地下
And when Bert drives that far underground...
警方就會沒有他的信號
the police will lose the signal from his wire.
但等他到達時 等待他的不是包而是你們三人
But when he arrives, instead of finding a bag he finds you three.
偽裝 武裝 危險
Disguised. Armed. Dangerous.
沒錯 但槍沒上膛 是吧?
Yeah, but the gun's not loaded, right?
當然 不會有人受傷 繼續
Of course not. Nobody gets hurt, come on.
然後我告訴他脫下外套和領帶
I then tell him to give me his jacket and tie.
讀讀這個:我身上還有現金 要開車去停車點
所以當警察開始急得直冒號時...
So just as the cops are starting to sweat...
爸爸按指令扔下新的紅色包包
Dad pulls out with the new red bag, just as he was instructed.
- 長官 我們又有信號了 - 謝天謝地
- Sir, we have the signal back. - Thank God.
只是開車的不是我父親 而是我們的替身
Only it won't be my father driving. It'll be our ringer.
- 我們重新找到他了 - 你怎麼知道是他?
- We're back on him, sir. - How do you know it's him?
現金還在我身上 我要去停車點
I still have the cash and I'm heading to the drop.
我想是他 跟著他
I guess it's him. Stay with him.
然後我開車到斯特普爾特中心
So I drive to the Staples Center.
國王對多倫多 熱門比賽 人群擁擠
Kings have Vancouver. Great matchup. Place will be packed.
警察會盯著錢 等綁匪收錢
Cops will stay with the money, wait for the kidnappers to receive the drop.
漢森投放了 盯好錢
Hanson made the drop, stay on the money.
我們發現要找的人了 抓住他
We got our man. Take him down.
趴下
Stay down.
婊娘養的
Son of a bitch.
到那時警察明白他們被...
By the time the cops know they've been had...
庫爾特就是幽靈替身
Kurt's a ghost.
尼克和黛爾帶著錢消失
And Nick and Dale disappear with the cash.
最後我也從監禁中獲救
And, finally, I am rescued from my hellish captivity.
謝謝 我父親呢?
Thank you. Where's my dad?
爸爸!
Dad!
一週後 風聲過去
A week later, once the smoke clears,
我們坐在泳池邊 分贓
we'll be sitting poolside, splitting up the cash.
錢到處飛舞 誰想要?足夠我們分
It's raining. Who wants it? There's enough to share.
看誰來了 誰想要些龍舌蘭?
Look what came. Who wants some tequila?
- 是現金 - 謝謝 寶貝
- It's cash. - Thanks, babe.
嗨 哇噢 黛爾
Hey, whoa, Dale.
把你孩子扔出去幻想中
Get your goddamn kids out of the fantasy.
讓他們享受泳池 讓我享受金錢
Let them enjoy the pool, let me enjoy the money.
他們都不被允許待在泳池
They're not even allowed at this pool.
我腦海裡去不掉
I can't turn my mind off.
- 伙伴們 伙伴們 伙伴們 - 你要阻止嗎?
- Guys. Guys. Guys. - Will you stop it?
得了 不要爭了 好嗎?
Come on. Let's not argue, okay?
我們想了個絕妙的計劃
We came up with an awesome plan.
很有才 太開創了
It is smart. It is mad creative.
你們又讓我印象深刻
You know, you boys continue to impress me.
- 我為你們驕傲 - 謝謝 哥們
- I'm proud of you. - Thanks, man.
- 但你才是想出大部分的那個 - 我沒有
- You came up with most of it, though. - I did not.
- 你有 - 那是謊話 是集體的功勞
- You did. - That is a lie. It was a team effort.
你想出了去車庫 切斷信號
You came up with going into the garage, losing the signal.
太妙了 小K想出了一次性手機那碼事
That was brilliant. Kurty came up with the dark-phone business.
- 那是從俠盜獵車手來的靈感 - 天才 黛爾...
- That's from "Grand Theft Auto." I took it. - Genius. Dale...
我想到了你從滑索下到蹦床然後滑板跑路
I had the thing where you go on the zip line to the trampoline to the skateboard.
如果你還記得 尼克否決了
Nick shot that down, if you remember.
沒錯 那不是個好主意
Yeah. It wasn't a good idea.
那是個糟糕的主意 實際上
It was a bad idea, it really was.
你老有一堆壞主意但最後拋磚引玉出好主意
You had a lot of bad ideas though that led to good ideas.
很有價值
And that is value.
謝謝 伙伴
Thanks, man.
好了 尼克 聽著 我的保證依舊有效
All right, Nick. Look, my word is still good.
如果你認為計劃不會成功 我們可以取消
You know, if you don't think it can work, we call it off.
由你決定 伙伴
It's up to you, buddy.
我們上哪去找不被追逐的手機?
Where do we get untraceable phones?
成了 這才是我們的好伙伴
There we go. That's our guy.
- 這傢伙 - 成了
- This guy. - There we go.
用比特幣預付過了
Prepaid with bitcoins.
越獄版
Jailbroken.
百分百不可追蹤
A hundred percent untraceable.
- 我們有了- 謝謝 可靠 謝謝 草你媽
- We got it. - Thanks. Solid. Thank you, Motherfucker.
祝好運 伙伴們
Good luck out there, boys.
- 他笑什麼? - 我只是祝好運
- What's that laugh about? - I just said good luck.
那是陰笑
That was a sinister giggle.
你陰笑著說這話
You said it with a sinister giggle.
我只是說也許你們需要一些設備
I'm just saying that maybe you guys might want a little advice.
- 伙伴們 那是可想而知的 不 謝謝 - 我們很好
- Boy, that was predictable. No, thanks. - We're good.
那你知道後續怎麼著嗎? 挫事一堆
You know what, then? Get the fuck on.
就是我說的 一堆挫事
That's what I said. Get the fuck on.
- 等等 - 我不喜歡這樣
- Wait a minute. - I don't like this.
- 我想聽聽他怎麼說 - 現在你想聽了?
- I wanna hear what he has to say. - Now you wanna hear?
你們綁架了一個
You got one on the hook.
會花去你們百分之五十一的錢
It'll cost 51 percent share of your company.
你想錯了
You're out of your fucking mind.
會花去你們百分之二的錢
It's gonna cost you 2 percent share of your company.
你討價還價的方式真怪異
So weird how you negotiate.
不需要了 你可以走了
It won't be in existence. You can have that.
- 還有轉寰餘地 - 給你們點建議 年輕人
- There's a middle ground. - Here's the advice, young men.
你們都是罪犯
Y'all criminals.
- 根本沒過好建議 - 我不接受
- It's never good advice. - I can't find the advice.
事實上 都不是真的 我們不是罪犯 對吧?
It's not even true, actually. We're not criminals. All right?
- 我們泥足深陷了 - 閉嘴
- We got dicked into this. - Shut up.
明白了 你們不能兩全其美
See, you can't have this both ways.
每次你們過來 你們看來就是
Every time you guys come here, you're like,
"我們是群快樂又幸運的傢伙"
"We're a bunch of happy-go-lucky guys.
我們沒有犯任何錯 卻又深陷困境
Through no fault of our own, we found ourselves in another pickle.
我們沒辦法抽身" 去他媽的
We can't get our fingers out of our asses." Fuck that.
你們是娘的罪犯 我們試圖謀殺老闆
You're fucking criminals. You've tried to kill your bosses.
到最後有一個人喪命 而現在你們幹綁票?
One of them ended up dead. And now you want to perpetrate a kidnapping?
你們三人是我這輩子見過的最瘋狂的草你媽罪犯
You three are the craziest motherfucking criminals I've ever seen in my life.
你們想要安全脫身?
You wanna pull this shit off?
你們就要那麼幹
You gotta act like it.
精闢
Word.
噢 真尷尬
Oh. That was embarrassing.
我們想要走個超級酷的慢貓步
We're trying to do a super cool slow-mo walk.
- 繼續 伙伴 - 放鬆
- Come on, man. - Easy.
- 過去了 我們走吧 - 去哪?
- It's over. Let's go. - Where you going?
幼稚的主意 我羞愧了
Moronic idea. I am mortified.
來嘛 哥們 我們繼續貓步
Come on, man. Let's do the walk.
你得堅持
You gotta stick with it.
你認為怎麼樣? 我需要再打自己兩拳?
What do you think? Should I beat myself up more?
不 你不需要再打自己了
No, you don't need to hit yourself anymore.
我想我們只要打電話就好了
I think we should just make the call.
等等 在我們開始前 我能說點什麼嗎?
Hold on. Before we kick this thing off, can I just say something?
我不是很 擅長這種事
I'm not really, good at this kind of thing, you know?
我媽媽在我四歲時去世...
My mom died when I was 4, and...
在你由伯特·漢森養大的情況下...
You know, when you're raised by Bert Hanson...
大部分朋友都是狐朋狗友
most of your friends are shitheads.
是的 我知道我把你們扯進這裡 但我很抱歉
Yeah. I know I dragged you guys into this, but I'm not sorry.
因為...
Because...
我真的很高興遇到你們
I'm really glad I met you guys.
不管怎樣 我希望你們收下這個
Anyway, I want you guys to have this.
- 是什麼? - 是鐵血戰士裡的用過的毒牙
- What is it? - It's an actual fang from Predator.
- 那部電影鐵血戰士? - 沒錯
- Predator the movie? - Yep.
我想把這個給你
I want you to have it.
- 真的? - 我發誓
- For real? - Swear to God.
你喜歡鐵血戰士嗎?
Do you like Predator?
是啊 我喜歡鐵血戰士
Yeah, I like Predator.
- 庫爾特呢? - 對 對 我也喜歡鐵血戰士
- Kurty? - Yeah. Yeah, I like Predator too.
我意思是我也喜歡 不是喜歡續集
I mean "also," not the sequel.
- 尼克呢? - 額 這個
- Nick? - Oh, well...
我第一次看鐵血戰士的時候不是很喜歡
I didn't like Predator when I first saw it...
但是我越來越喜歡了
but it grew on me quite a bit.
我很喜歡鐵血戰士
I like Predator a great deal.
我們在說他還是電影
Are we talking about him or Predator?
我討厭話裡有話
I'm terrible with metaphors.
- 來讓我們打電話吧 - 你們把我搞糊塗了
- Let's make the phone call. - It was lost on me.
很多事都這樣
Most things are.
你好
Yeah.
你們收到那筆錢了嗎?
You got that cash?
- 是的 我收到了 - 耶
- Yeah, I got it. - Yeah.
現在我需要你大搖大擺的走到第四街大橋
Now, I want you to sashay up to the 4th Street Bridge.
你會在半路上發現有一個板凳 坐下來
You're gonna find a bench about halfway up, take a load off.
你單獨帶著我們說好的錢來
And you bring the amount that we agreed upon and you come alone.
如果你這麼做了
And if you do,
你兒子就能速速的回家
you will find your son returned home lickety-splickety.
第四街大橋 他會把他扔到那
Fourth Street Bridge, he's gonna have him drop it over the side.
現在 我希望所有地方都在
Now, I want every inch covered,
安全距離內覆蓋警力
but everyone holds a safe distance.
好的 但是距離也別太安全 懂了嗎?
Yeah, but not too safe a distance. Understand?
這個包是你最重要的東西
This bag is your number fucking one priority.
不 實際上 我兒子才是最重要的
No, actually, your son's life is our number one priority.
是的 你知道我什麼意思
Yeah, you know what I mean.
或許我知道吧
Yeah, I think I do.
誰能看清?
Does anybody have a visual?
大橋上仍然是空的 老大
Bridge is still clear, chief.
漢森預計兩分鐘到達
Hanson approaching. ETA, two minutes.
刀鋒戰士已就位
The Blade is in position.
銀河護衛 就位
Majestic, in position.
我就...
I am in...
人間凶器已就位
Kill Shot is in position.
- 哇 人間凶器? - 是的 我想當人間凶器
- Whoa, "Kill Shot"? - Yeah, I wanna be Kill Shot.
所以你就是人間凶器了 我喜歡
Then you are Kill Shot. I love it.
好可愛的名字啊 尼克
Pretty sweet name there, Nick.
哦 如果我們用了代號就別叫真名了 黛爾
Ooh.We don't wanna use real names if we're using code names, Dale.
別把我名字說出來 庫爾特
Don't say my name, Kurt.
我那是意外 你是故意的
Mine was an accident. Yours was on purpose.
- 我不覺得你是無心的 - 你說什麼?
- I don't think yours was an accident. - What?
為什麼我們在一個房間裡還用對講機
Why are we on walkie-talkies in the same room?
我們是在檢查設備
We're checking the equipment.
我們不用這樣 他會出現在電視遙控裡
We don't need to. He's on a TV remote control.
我想參加 我沒事幹
I was trying to participate. I didn't have anything to...
嘿 把持住 刀鋒戰士看見他在這了 他在這
Hey. Hold up. The Blade's got a visual. He's here. He's here.
- 我們走 - 哦 操
- Here we go. - Oh, shit.
- 一切正常 人間凶器打電話 - 我正在打了
- All right. Kill Shot, make the call. - I'm dialing. Here we go.
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
嘿 那是什麼聲音 誰在給你打電話?
Hey, what's that? Who's calling you?
- 我不知道 沒顯示號碼 - 哦 不
- I don't know. It's blocked. - Oh, no.
- 你好 - 嗨
- Hello. - Hi.
- 你是誰? - 是我 小崽子
- Who is this? - It's me, dickless.
你應該打那個電話
You're supposed to call the dark phone.
它正在你的手上 說好把它黏到板凳上的
It's in your hand. You were to tape that under the bench.
不 這不是 哦 等等
No, that's not... Oh, wait.
哦 去死吧 所以 他那是什麼手機?
Oh, shit. So, what phone does he have?
伯特那 是有我們聯絡方式的庫爾特的手機
Bert has Kurt's phone with our contact information on it.
而且還有我們以前做朋友的照片?
And the pictures of us from when we used to be friends?
別鬧了 你看 沒什麼大不了的
Knock it off. Look, this is no big deal.
我們等到明天再幹
We'll do it tomorrow.
我們不打電話他就找不到手機
As long as we don't call, he'll never find it.
他找到了
He found it.
- 他怎麼了? - 我們死定了
- He what? How? - We are screwed.
- 操 - 等等 等等 我有辦法了 我有辦法了
- Shit. - Wait, wait, wait. I got an idea. I got an idea.
給你手機打電話
Call your phone.
如果他接聽了就不能看它了
If he's talking, he's not gonna look through it.
- 你電話號碼是多少? - 你不知道?
- What's your number? - You don't know?
我不知道我的號碼
I don't know my number.
我不知道 我從來不給我自己打電話
I don't know. I never call myself.
我知道你們倆的電話號碼 323...
I know both of your numbers. 323...
- 這就夠了 我來 我來 - 好
- That's all I need. I got there. Here we go. - Okay, yes.
- 來 好 好 對 - 好 可以了
- Here we go. Okay. All right. Ahem. - Right, okay.
有電話進來 鈴聲是凱蒂·派瑞的咆哮
Call coming in. "Roar" by Katy Perry.
這些小崽子們很自信啊
These guys are confident.
耶 你好
Yeah, hello.
看起來像蚱蜢發現自己
Look like the grasshopper found himself...
- 坐在小草上 - 有點過了
- ...a blade of grass to sit upon. - Too much.
- 你好 - 來讓我們結束這一切吧 假牛仔
- Hello. - Let's get this over with, pretend cowboy.
來 聽著 我命令你接下來去曼德拉草酒店
Now, listen, I need you to proceed to the Mandrake Hotel.
我要你去地下停車場
I need you to go underground into parking.
4421號位置
I need you to get to Spot 4421.
你會看見一個大舊包在那 裝滿它
You're gonna see a big old bag there. Fill it up.
然後接著北上到菲格羅阿
And then I need you to proceed north onto Figueroa
等待我的下一步指示
and await further instructions.
等等 等等
Wait, wait.
你以為我們不知道你和警察在一起嗎
And don't think we don't know you got the law with you.
我們都知道
That's something we do know.
對嗎? 所以如果他們跟你去車庫...
All right? So if any of them cavalry follow you down in the garage...
我會像打撲克一樣打你兒子的屁股
I'm personally gonna stick a hot poker so far up your son's ass...
我要把他的牙打成爆米花
I'm gonna pop his teeth like popcorn!
看到了嗎? 我們回到了正軌上
See? We're back on track.
我必須把手機拿回來 裡面有好多私密照片
I gotta get that phone back. So many dick pics.
- 真的? - 是的 雖然不都是我的
- Really? - Yeah, not all mine, though.
交通比賽開始 他不到十分鐘就能到 我們怎麼辦?
With game-time traffic, he could be here in less than 10 minutes. How we doing?
- 差不多了 - 服務生的衣服去哪了?
- Almost done. - Where are the bellhop costumes?
- 什麼? - 服務生的衣服
- What? - Bellhop costumes.
我們不是要穿著服務生的衣服逃走嗎?
Aren't we dressed as bellhops when we escape with the money?
那裡沒有服務生
This place doesn't have bellhops.
- 沒有? - 沒有
- It doesn't? - No.
我以為那有一些小甜心呢
I thought there was supposed to be some sweet-ass...
- 這是什麼鬼東西? - 今天可不是鬼節
- What the fuck are these? - It's not Halloween.
- 我在最短的時間內只能做到這樣了 - 這個不嚇人
- Best I could do on short notice. - It's not scary.
- 嘿 我看起來怎麼樣? - 你是什麼鬼?
- Hey, how do I look? - Who the hell are you?
- 我是庫爾特 - 我知道
- It's me, Kurt. - I know that part.
太糟糕了 你看起來不像伯特 像馬克吐溫
Terrible. You don't look like Bert, you look like Mark Twain.
沒有一件事是按照計劃來的 一切都搞砸了
None of this is like I pictured when we were planning it. Everything was cooler.
他遠看還是不錯的
He just has to look good from a distance.
- 我們走 開始吧 - 我們動手吧
- Here we go. Let's do it. - Let's roll.
我們只要各就各位有信心我們就會好好的
Let's just do what we gotta do, do it confidently and, we should be fine.
- 我們走 - 哦
- Here we go. - Oh.
- 嗨 小伙子們 - 哦 嗨
- Hi, boys. - Oh, hi.
你住在酒店
You staying at the hotel,
還是這是你的酒店? 你在這住嗎?
or is this your hotel? You staying here?
從你們闖進我的辦公室開始我一直關注著你們
I've been keeping my eye on you since you broke into my office.
我不知道這裡發生了什麼 而且我一點也不關心
I don't know what's going on here, and I don't give a shit.
你為什麼在這? 你想要什麼?
Why are you here? What do you want?
我感覺你知道我想要什麼
I think you know what I want.
不 我是不會和你上床的
No, I'm not gonna sleep with you.
這個瘋女人在想什麼啊?
Why can't this crazy bitch get it through her head?
- 放尊重點 對不起 - 你在耍我嗎?
- Keep it respectful. Sorry. - Are you kidding me?
- 別這麼說她 - 我在努力搞清這件事
- Don't call her that. - I'm gonna make this simple.
我要叫警察來把你們送到監獄裡去
I'm gonna call the police and send you to jail.
- 別這樣 - 別啊
- Don't do that. - Come on.
除非黛爾上我
Unless Dale plows me.
為什麼? 為什麼是我? 我有什麼特別的?
Why? Why me? What is so special about me?
這是個合理的疑問 所有人都想知道
That's a fair question. Everybody's wondering.
- 我也是 - 黛爾你有收藏過什麼東西嗎?
- I am. - Did you ever collect anything, Dale?
- 不要讓他捲入這件事 - 我收藏什麼?
- Don't get him going on this. - What do I collect?
- 可多了 - 布朗百科全書?
- Tons of stuff. - Encyclopedia Brown?
- 新的豆豆娃娃不算 - 銀河戰星
- New Beanie Babies, makes no sense. - Battlestar Galactica.
好吧 我會收藏一些東西 怎麼了?
Fine. I collect some stuff. Why?
好吧 我收藏雞雞
Okay, well, I collect cocks.
- 齒輪? - 朱莉亞
- Cogs? - Julia.
- 雞雞 - 哦 額 好吧
- "Cocks." - Oh, yeah. Well...
就在這
Right up here.
我有一個陳列著滿滿的雞雞們的陳列室
I've got quite an impressive trophy room filled with cocks.
- 我們就在這 - 別
- We're in there. - Don't.
在夜裡 我閉上我的雙眼
And at night, when I close my eyes...
我回想它們
I reflect on them...
我排列它們
I alphabetize them...
我為它們拂去塵埃
I dust them.
它們為什麼落灰了?
Why are they dusty?
但是還有一個小問題 黛爾
But there's one little problem, Dale.
看到那個地方了嗎? 壁爐上面空蕩蕩的地方?
See that space? That empty space above the fireplace?
- 看到了嗎? - 你缺一隻雞雞?
- See that? - You got a cock missing?
這是為我十一歲起
That's reserved for the only man who's ever said no to this.
唯一說不的男人留個位置
Since I was 11 years old.
就是你 黛爾
That's you, Dale.
我的白鯨
My white whale.
哦 好吧 我很感激 真的 我猜那很甜蜜
Oh, okay. Well, I appreciate that. I really do. That's sweet, I guess.
但是 嘿 現在有個辦法 我的朋友庫爾特喜歡開墾荒田
But, hey, here's an idea. My friend Kurt here loves to plow.
- 而且他一定比我厲害 - 絕對的
- And maybe he could jump in for me... - Absolutely.
我可以補充一下 我有真的活好
I could pinch-plow. I got a real green thumb.
我們都知道這會兒聊上癮了
We all know this is just the addiction talking.
如果你想要的不止快速解決...
If you're looking for more than a quick fix...
我可以給你提供一樣富有含義還持久的東西
I can provide you something that's very meaningful, long-lasting.
什麼? 你在說什麼?
What? What are you talking about?
我在說我們
I'm talking about us.
- 我們? 我們所有人? - 不
- Us? All of us? - No.
- 那就更好了 - 不
- That's even better. - No.
越多越好 我喜歡這個點子
More the merrier. I love this idea.
你們有很多堅挺的東西
You got a lot of stuff sticking out.
我有很多洞做它們的去處
I got a lot of holes going in.
晚上有一點你們必須要搞清楚
At one point of the night, you'd better make sure that,
就只有一個棍棍在洞洞裡
that one is in this one.
- 謝謝 - 那不是我的意思 我誤解了
- Thank you. - That's not what I meant. You misunderstood.
我去梳洗一下 你們要做點什麼準備嗎?
I'm gonna go freshen up. Why don't you guys suck each other off to get ready?
- 我們來吧 - 你在幹什麼?
Here we go. - What are you doing?
什麼? 她讓我們上她?
What? She's making us fuck her.
- 我誰都不睡 - 謝謝
- I'm not gonna fuck anyone. - Thank you.
我願意和她做愛 如果她需要的話
I'm willing to make love to her, if that's required.
- 你是認真的嗎? - 我可以借用一下這個剃刀嗎?
- Are you serious? - Can I borrow this razor?
可以 隨便用
Yeah. Go nuts.
有什麼要求嗎?  捆綁?  旋轉?
Any requests? Landing strip? Dinner roll?
隨便啦 我們趕時間 謝謝
Whatever's there. We're in a rush. Thanks.
我不想出軌
I don't wanna commit adultery on my wife.
不 如果你是為了救你的家庭就不是出軌好嗎
No, it's not adultery if you're doing it to save your family. Okay?
你覺得你在監獄裡關三十年
You think Stacy and your girls are gonna wait for you...
史黛西和你的孩子們會等你?
...while you're in prison for 30 years?
他們不會的
They're not.
我們就不能想想辦法嗎?
Can't we just come up with some kind of plan, though?
哦 好 絕對的 我有辦法了 好 我們走
Oh, yes. Absolutely. I got a plan. Okay, here we go. Areas.
我選屁股 臉 陰道
I'll go butt, face, puss.
我不要進陰道 這讓我最有負罪感臉
I cannot go in the puss. That'll make me the most guilty.
好吧 這樣行不行? 屁股 臉 陰道
Good call. How about this? Butt, face, puss.
這才是我該去的地方
That's where I should be.
我們在談論哪... 這主意不錯
I'm talking about a way where... That's good.
如果我們換位置她就會忘了誰在哪
If we're switching positions, she'll lose track of who's where.
- 就像賭博 - 三張牌的賭博
- Like the shell game. - Three-card Monte. Exactly.
我可以埋胸然後打她屁股
I can motorboat her boobies and then smack on her butt.
只要不是低俗可恥的方式就行
So long as nothing is done in a cheap or degrading way.
- 我們會像菲爾醫生一樣敏感 - 我不知道我能不能上她
- We'll be as sensitive as Dr. Phil. - I don't know if I can fuck this woman.
想想你的老婆孩子們
Think about your wife and girls.
想想我的孩子們 我可以做到的
I'll think about my girls. I can get it done.
好了嗎?
All right?
- 史黛西 - 哦 不
- Stacy. - Oh, no.
- 你怎麼找到我的? - 來這裡多會兒了?
- How did you find me? - Been there a while?
手機定位
Find My iPhone.
- 我知道你是騙我的 - 不 我不是
- I knew you were cheating on me. - No, I'm not.
- 他不是 我們正準備去蹲監獄 - 監獄?
- He's not. We're trying to stay out of prison. - Prison?
沒有人會進監獄的
No one's going to prison.
- 因為我們綁架了一個人 - 綁架?
- Because we were gonna kidnap someone. - Kidnapping?
- 不 首先 那個人是綁架了他自己 - 對
- No. First, the man kidnapped himself. - That's right.
- 他逼我們... - 黛爾 甚至不操逼
- He forced us... - Dale wouldn't even do puss.
- 我從沒想過操逼 - 我兩次都選的屁股
- I didn't even wanna do the puss. - I chose ass both times.
我說那會讓我最有罪惡感
I said puss will make me the most guilty.
你們沒在幫我! 閉嘴!
You're not helping me! Shut up!
你看 這事太傻逼了 寶貝兒
Look, this is such a stupid thing, honey.
而且放輕鬆 這裡還沒發生過性交
And easy, and nothing sexual is even happening here.
來吧 黛爾 小妹妹不會把你吃了的
Come on, Dale, this pussy isn't gonna eat itself.
- 朱莉亞? - 史黛西
- Julia? - Stacy.
還有孩子們
And the babies.
看這些孩子們 黛爾  她們和你好像
Look at those babies. Oh, Dale, they look just like you.
- 聽著 - 你有病
- Listen to me. - You are sick.
我沒病 別這樣 可以讓我...?
I'm not sick. Please. Can I just...?
別跟著我 別跟著我
Do not follow me. Do not follow me.
你這個小婊子
You fucking bitch.
對不起 沒想到會這樣
Sorry. Really didn't mean for that to happen.
好了 朱莉亞 你想性交嗎?
Okay, Julia. You wanna fuck?
是啊
Yeah.
為什麼不呢 是嗎? 我的婚姻已經結束了 它完全被毀了
Why not, right? My marriage is over. It's basically ruined.
所以我毀了你的陰道怎麼樣? 這聽起來好嗎?
So how about I ruin that pussy? That sound good?
- 不不不 你是負責臉 - 我是陰道
- No, no, no. You're face. - I'm puss.
- 耶 - 不不不 這都是我的
- Yeah. - No, no, no. This one's all mine.
什麼?
What?
- 來吧 我們洗澡的時候來一發 - 太好了
- Let's do it. Let's do it in the shower. - Attaboy.
你想這樣嗎? 那裡潮濕又美好
Is that what you want? Nice and wet in here.
- 我無法拯救我的婚姻了 - 是的 你不能
- I can't save my marriage from prison. - No, you can't.
- 幹得漂亮 黛爾 - 開始行動吧
- Great, Dale. - Let's roll.
- 我們失去了聯繫 - 靠
- We lost the wire. - Shit.
我們要開輛便車進去嗎?
Should we send in an unmarked?
我們不能冒險 我們就守在這
We can't risk it. We'll hold here.
你好 你好嗎
Hello. Howdy-do.
- 你走這邊 - 停
- You go on this side. - Stop.
嘿
Hey.
這是什麼鬼東西?
What the fuck is this?
我不需要和你爭辯
I do not need that sass-mouth.
我要的是那袋現金 現在 把它拿過來
What I need is that sack of cash. Now, get it over here.
別把它扔給我 滑過來 再來一次
Don't you throw it at me. You slide it. Do it again.
- 不 就放到這吧 - 檢查一下
- No, we'll keep it here. - Check it.
- 我的天 - 看那裡
- Holy shit. - Lookie there.
- 我們做到了 - 真是個好包
- We did it. - There's a pretty bag.
好 好吧 嘿
Okay. All right. Hey.
我還要那個黏在凳子上被你拿走的手機
I'll also take that phone you took from the bottom of that bench.
什麼?
What?
- 手機 把手機給我 - 把手機給他
- The cell phone. Give me the cell phone. - Throw the phone to him.
現在把你花俏的外套和領帶給我
Now that fancy jacket and that snappy tie.
- 脫掉拿過來 - 不要
- Get them off. Get them over. - No.
- 他說"不" - 我認為他是這麼說的
- He say "no"? - I think he said no.
但是我們拿到這個了
But we got this.
不要逼我用這個六髮式手槍
Don't make me use this six-shooter.
男人手裡有槍
Man's got a shooter.
你讓我感到噁心
You make me sick.
美國的病根就在你這種人身上 每個人都想得到施捨
You're what's wrong with America. Everyone just wants a handout.
拿去吧 拿去吧 從老老實實賺錢的人們身上拿去吧
Take, take, take from the people who earn their money honestly.
好吧 我們現在不聊了 男人手裡真的有槍
All right, let's not chitchat now. The man does have a gun.
你真會說話 但我能一槍斃了你
You got a real lip on you. I will shoot you in the chest.
好吧 來吧 斃了我吧
Well, go ahead. Shoot me.
你壓根就沒種
You don't have the balls.
他有的 他的種可大著呢
Yeah, he does. He got big old balls.
大嘴巴一個 再沒其他能力了
Big mouth. Nothing behind it.
- 伙伴 - 我的天啊
- Dude. - Oh, my God.
- 搞毛啊 - 我的天啊
- What the fuck? - Oh, my God.
你做了什麼
What did you do?
- 你斃了他 - 我沒有
- You shot him. - No, I didn't.
- 你斃了他 - 手槍不應該是負荷的
- You did. - That was not supposed to be loaded.
- 你什麼意思 - 這不是我的錯
- What do you mean? - That's not my fault.
- 我的天啊 - 等一下...
- Oh, my God. - Wait, hold...
伙伴 你們開始互相譴責的時候
Man. You should've seen your faces right now...
應該看看自己的臉
when you started blaming each other.
怎麼了
What's happening right now?
我利用了你們
I'm fucking you over.
不會的 我們是朋友啊
No, no. But we're all friends now.
是啊 但這是多麼大的一個轉折 不是嗎
We are, but what a great twist, right?
我最初想要拿走全部的錢 再栽贓給你們幾個
At first I was just gonna take all the money and throw you guys under the bus.
但是我想 得了吧
I mean, come on. Duh.
但是當老爸叫了警察後 證明他根本不關心我
But then when Dad called the cops and proved he doesn't give a fuck about me...
我才意識到 既然我能繼承他的財產
I realized, why take a few of his millions...
你們也能替我頂罪 我為什麼還要拿走他幾百萬中的一小部分
when I can inherit all of them and you guys can take the fall?
過一會 警察就會來
In minutes, the police will be down here
發現是你們殺了我可憐的爸爸
and discover that you killed my poor father...
用的是你綁架我時從我房間偷來的槍
with a gun you stole from my room when you abducted me.
那是假話
That is a lie!
- 他知道 - 他知道的
- He knows. - He knows. He knows.
別擔心 伙伴們
Don't worry, guys.
我來解決
I'll take it from here.
抱歉 雷克斯
Sorry, Rex.
我們錄下證據了
But we got you.
既然我能繼承他所有的財產
Why take a few of his millions...
又能栽贓給你們幾個 為何還要在乎他區區幾百萬
when I can inherit all of them and you guys can take the fall?
噢 將你一技 賤人
Ooh. Checkmate, bitch.
- 好吧 給我吧 - 好吧 好吧
- All right, here. Let's have that. - Yeah. Yeah.
- 不 我...好吧 抱歉 - 謝謝 伙伴
- No, I... Right. Sorry. - Thanks, man.
不想多拿幾分鐘嗎
Didn't wanna hold onto that for two more minutes?
不用 那是別人送的禮物
No, that was a gift.
- 你把普銳斯停在後巷了嗎 - 停了
- Did you park the Prius in the back alley? - I sure did.
- 你有鑰匙嗎 - 這裡
- Do you have the keys? - Here you go.
我真為你們驕傲
I'm really proud of you guys.
說真的 你們像一個隊伍一樣團結
Seriously. You pulled together. You worked like a team.
和我們計劃的一樣
Just like we planned.
黛爾 我們開了很多玩笑
Dale, we had a lot of laughs.
我很感激 你使我感到高興
I really appreciate it. I mean, you made me smile.
尼克 我想讓你更搞笑
Nick, I want you to smile more.
知道嗎 看你眉頭皺的
You know? Look at those frown lines.
休個假放鬆放鬆
Take a vacation. Lighten up.
- 庫爾特 我覺得我可能最想你了 - 為什麼
- Kurt, I think I'm gonna miss you the most. - Why?
好吧
Okay.
拜拜
Bye.
接著
Catch.
- 別... - 我的天啊
- Don't... - Goddamn it.
抱歉 我剛好接住了 我去 等一下
Sorry. I just have good hands. Fuck. Hang on a second.
站住 站住
Hey, freeze. Freeze.
黛爾 得了吧 你覺得我會給你一個負荷的槍
Dale, come on. You think I'd give you a loaded gun?
我去
Shit.
我要走了 我要去倉庫等著被警察營救 再見
I gotta get going. Gotta wait to be saved at the warehouse by the cops. See you.
我去 好好跟警察談 你全身都是你爸爸的血
Oh, shit. Good luck talking to the cops. You have your dad's blood all over... Oh!
我們就不能給自己留點話嗎
Can we not keep anything to ourselves?
我去 抱歉
Fuck me. I'm so sorry.
這比我做的還糟 我做了些什麼
That's worse than what I did. What did I do?
你是他的朋友 你把他介紹給我
You're friends with him. You introduced me.
我們不會害怕你那個沒子彈的槍 雷克斯 你個白痴
We're not gonna be afraid of an unloaded gun, Rex, you dipshit.
他有子彈 他有子彈
He's got bullets. He's got bullets.
他有子彈 哇靠
He's got bullets? Fucking hell.
庫爾特 你多大腰圍 32嗎
Kurt, what are you? A 32 waist?
- 哇靠 他要強姦我們 - 不會
- Oh, dear God. He's gonna rape us. - No.
- 你剛想要我... - 他只是想要褲子
- Oh, you just want my... - He just wants the pants.
你們就出些餿主意
All-time shittiest idea you guys ever had.
真不敢相信你們說服我趟這趟渾水
Can't believe you talked me into this.
- 這個人已經死了 - 我知道
- This guy's dead now. - I know that.
- 他死了 - 我們就應該繼續做齒輪
- He's dead. - We should've stayed cogs.
這他媽的要耗太久
This is taking too damn long.
我擦
Shit.
這不是袋子的問題
This isn't about the bag.
這是個該死的陷阱
This is the goddamn drop.
進去 現在所有人都進去
Move in. Everybody move in now.
脫下那條有血跡的褲子
Take off the incriminating pants.
難道我要穿著內褲跑嗎
Run around in my underwear?
為什麼不扔到車箱裡 我們可是有五百萬
Why not throw the body in the trunk? We got 5 million bucks.
到處都是警察 我們哪都去不了
There's police everywhere. We're not gonna get away.
該死
Oh, shit.
- 拿上袋子 趕緊上車 - 為什麼
- Grab the bag. Get the fuck in. - Why?
在你們那小子到倉庫前 我們要把警察引過去
Lead the cops to that warehouse before your boy gets there.
如果他們看到他自由走動 他們可能就會相信你們 走吧
If they see him out walking free, they just might believe your ass. Let's go.
拿上錢
Get the money.
嘿 黑 伙伴們
Hey. Hey, guys.
哇靠 是這群混蛋
Goddamn it. It's those idiots.
我知道我從為說過關於綁架的事情
I knew I never said anything about kidnapping.
來吧 我們走吧
Come on. Let's go.
跟蹤我們已經是他們計劃的一部分
Following us is already a part of their plan.
你根本不知道 只是確認一下
You never know. Wanna make sure.
誰繫上安全帶了
What is the seat-belt situation?
- 我繫上了 - 我們需要繫上
- I got mine. - We should put them on.
- 我能跟你系一個嗎 - 抓住儀錶盤
- Can I get under yours? - Hold on to the dashboard.
- 我擦 - 這條路不對
- Shit. - This is the wrong way.
這條路不對 掉頭 趕緊停車
This is the wrong way. Turn around. Stop the car.
- 你在跟誰發簡訊 - 我女朋友
- Who you texting? - My lady.
- 放下 - 如果我不讓她知道 她會發瘋的
- Put it down. - If I don't check in, she goes crazy.
順便問一下
By the way,
你們一開始在那個車庫裡搞什麼呢
what the hell were you doing back there in that garage in the first place?
那是什麼
What's that, now?
- 哇靠 - 怎麼了
- Holy shit. - What's going on?
你在那裡偷贖金
You were down there to steal the ransom money.
聽著 我是去搶的 不是偷的
Listen, I hustle, I don't steal.
你說些什麼 你在車庫裡做什麼
What the fuck does that...? What were you doing in the garage?
我在想那是個機會
I was thinking there was a chance...
你們拿不到錢 情況越來越糟 而且那個人會殺了你們三個
the drop might go south, and that guy would kill y'all.
在那個情況 你們應該讓我拿錢而不是他
And in such a scenario, you'd rather me have the cash than him.
- 他在賭我們辦不到 - 你個混蛋
- He was betting against us. - You motherfucker.
- 我只是對你們即將面臨的死亡表示尊重 - 尊重我們
- I was honoring your potential death. - Honoring us?
我們是什麼 日本武士
What are we, samurai?
等一下 喂 是火車
Wait, hold on. Oh, hey. Train.
- 有火車 有火車 - 有火車
- Train! Train! Train! - Train!
- 漂亮 喔喔 - 該死
- Nice! Woo-hoo! - Damn it.
你就是這麼擺脫警察的
That's how you lose the cops.
- 我們不應該擺脫警察 - 不要擺脫警察
- We're not supposed to lose the cops. - Don't lose the cops.
這是整個主意
That's the whole idea.
- 好想法 - 現在回去 就更好了
- It was a good thought. - Going back. This is great.
我希望你開慢點 你就不會犯錯了
I wish you'd slow down. You wouldn't make mistakes.
別批評他了 他已經做到最好了
Don't criticize the man. He's doing the best he can.
到了 我會讓他們知道的 等一下
Here, I'll let them know. Hold on.
嘿 我們回來了 我們會在這
Hey. We're back. We'll stay here...
直到火車走了
till all this shit goes by.
然後我們一起走
Then we'll all roll.
這幾個傻蛋在幹什麼
What the fuck are these assholes doing?
- 他們懂了 - 應該是
- They get that? - Yeah, I think so.
- 你車上載的是什麼啊 - 那是什麼
- What's that you're carrying around? - What is that?
是給我的小貓的
It's for my kitties.
- 你還有小貓 - 驚奇吧
- You got kittens? - Surprising.
- 我不能有小貓嗎 - 你為什麼總是指責一切
- I can't have kittens? - Why you always jumping on everything?
- 你帶著貓架到處跑很奇怪的 - 我喜歡小貓
- It's weird you're hauling around a cat stand. - I love pussy.
- 嘿 我能下車撒尿嗎 - 不行 我們現在在飛車追逐
- Hey, can I hop out and piss? - No. We're in a car chase.
超級長的火車 我可以尿完的
Super long train. I feel I could get it done.
車上這麼多貨物
It is a lot of freight.
堅持下去
Hold the line
可能需要...
It probably needs...
愛不總是能即使到達
Love isn't always on time
堅持 堅持
Hold the line
這也太容易了
It's just too goddamn easy.
我感覺我現在可以去尿了
I feel like I could have pissed by now.
讓他去 開門
Let him go. Open the door.
- 還有一節車 - 該死
- Caboose coming. - Shit.
該死 條子
Oh, shit. Cops.
- 條子 條子 - 該死
- Cops. Cops. - Shit.
- 怎麼了 - 你丟了東西
- What happened? - You lost your stuff.
- 什麼 該死 - 是的 你丟了你的貓架
- What? Damn it. - Yeah, you lost your cat stuff.
好了 這有個人 當心他
Okay, there's a man there. Watch out for him.
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey! Hey!
- 我們困在裡面了 - 不會太久
- Hey, we're boxed in here. - Not for long.
- 不要 不要 - 我一直想這麼做了
- No, no, no. - I've always wanted to do this.
最後再來一次
Gotta make it last
我輕撫你一次
I touch you once
我輕撫你兩次
I touch you twice
該死
Shit.
幹嘛
What?
這是哪
So where is this place?
快到了 橋下面
It's up here. Under the bridge.
- 你在幹什麼 - 你應該在橋下走
- What are you doing? - You're supposed to go under the bridge.
放鬆
Relax.
- 輪子被卡住了 - 踩煞車器
- The wheels are locked. - Pump the brakes.
- 換擋 - 停車
- Shift down. - Put it in park.
我沒辦法思考
I can't think.
我賭你們現在一定愛死這個圍欄了
Bet y'all loving this fence now.
我已經從這些圍欄中恢復意識了
I've come around to the whole fence thing.
我也愛死安全帶了
I would've loved a seat belt too.
好吧 下一步計劃是什麼 蠢貨
Well, what's the next part of the plan, Motherfucker?
這裡 這裡 這裡
There. There. There.
- 嘿 嘿 他不在這 我們贏了 - 什麼
- Hey. Hey, he's not here. We beat him. - What?
- 我們贏了 - 嘿
- We beat him. - Hey.
幹得好
Hey, nice job...
- 那個蠢蛋在哪 - 我不知道
- Where's Motherfucker? - I don't know.
條子 條子
Cops. Cops.
嘿
Hey.
- 下車 - 容易
- Get out of the car. - Easy.
- 舉起手來 - 放鬆 把槍放地上
- Hands up. - Relax. Please, put your guns down.
我們沒有殺任何人 我向老天發誓
We didn't kill anybody. I swear to God.
我不吃這套 跟法官說這些吧
I don't give a goddamn. Tell it to the judge.
我們沒有綁架任何人
We didn't kidnap anybody.
他綁架了他自己 他隨時都會溜進來
He kidnapped himself. He'll sneak in any second.
- 他本應該捆在椅子上的 - 他在你後面
- He was supposed to be tied up to that chair. - Right behind you.
誰 他
Who? Him?
是的
Yeah.
啊哦 完蛋了 完大蛋了
Aw, that looks bad. That looks bad.
- 這個該死貨 - 你應該相信我們
- This fucking guy. - You gotta believe us.
是他們 他們三個拷打我 他們說他們要殺了我爸爸
That's them. Those three, they tortured me, then said they were gonna kill my dad.
- 別聽他胡說 - 就在車庫
- Oh, don't listen to that. - That's garbage.
告訴我他沒事
Tell me he's okay. Please.
- 我很抱歉 孩子 - 不
- I'm sorry, son. - No.
- 不 - 他殺了他爸爸啊
- No. - He killed his father.
- 他真是演技派 厲害 - 不要相信他
- He's a very strong actor. Bravo. - Don't buy it.
- 趴下 - 我們這就趴下
- Get on the ground. - We're getting down.
難以置信你相信了他的演技
I can't believe you're buying that acting.
他演得的確很逼真 但是
I mean, it's good, but...
你有權利保持沉默 蠢貨們
You have the right to remain silent, assholes.
你也有權利請律師 你們有
You have the right to an attorney, asshole. You have...
嘿 嘿 那是我的手機 他手上有我的手機
Hey. Hey, that's my phone. He has my phone.
- 那是伯特在長凳瞎買年拿的電話 - 檢查一下
- The phone Bert had on the bench. - Check that phone.
如果他一直被捆在這裡
If he was tied up here the whole time,
雷克斯怎麼拿到他的手機的
how could Rex have the same phone?
- 他們換了褲子 - 是的 他們明白了
- They switched pants! - Yeah. They got it.
- 檢查一下 - 只是同一個鈴聲 長官
- Check it. - It's the same ringtone, sir.
是的 那是我的手機
Yeah. That's my phone.
我有相同的鈴聲 這是個振奮人心的鈴聲
I have the same ringtone. It's an inspiring ringtone.
你一直待在這裡 還帶著手機
You were here this whole time with a cell phone...
但是卻沒有打給警察
and didn't bother to call the police?
- 是的 - 閉上你們的狗嘴
- Yes. - Shut the fuck up.
讓我看看
Let me see it.
我說了 讓我看看
I said let me see it.
好的
Okay.
大家都退後
Everybody move the fuck off.
他現在看起來有罪了 對吧
Yeah, he looks pretty guilty now, right?
他絕對是嫌疑犯
He's definitely suspect.
扔掉你們的槍
Drop your fucking guns.
對這個混蛋開槍 趕緊對他開槍
You shoot this prick. You shoot this prick right now.
扔下槍 不然我就打爆他的頭 聽到沒 快點
You drop your guns or I'll blow his fucking head off. You hear me? Move.
快點
Move.
他準備就這樣逃跑
He's gonna get away with this.
- 這傢伙不會停下 - 他真是堅韌不拔
- This guy doesn't quit. - He's incredibly resilient.
- 你 車裡有鑰匙嗎 - 有
- You. Keys in the car? - Keys are in the car.
- 這個賤人 - 冷靜
- This fucking guy. - Calm down.
這個賤人都是學我的 "冷靜 黛爾" 不
This fucking guy took everything from me. "Calm down, Dale"? No.
- 這個賤人去死吧 他害我失去妻子 - 好吧 走開
- Fuck this fucking guy. He took my wife. - All right, step away.
還害我失去了孩子 我要做點什麼
He took my kids. I'm gonna do something.
冷靜 你要做什麼
Easy. What are you gonna do?
看看誰現在才是掠奪者
Look who's the predator now, bitch.
等一下 黛爾 你要幹什麼
Wait, Dale. What are you doing?
- 黛爾 - 我中槍了
- Dale. - Oh, I'm shot.
過去 抓住他
Get in there. Get him.
銬住這個瘋子 順便在痛扁他一頓
Cuff this crazy asshole. And beat the shit out of him while you're at it.
- 噢 該死 - 黛爾 伙伴 你還好嗎 喂
- Oh, shit. - Dale, buddy, you okay? Hey.
- 我的天啊 - 喔噢
- Oh, my God. - Oh, wow.
- 該死 - 你剛剛在幹嘛
- Oh, shit. - What was that?
黛爾 放下這個 你這到底是什麼計劃 伙伴
Dale, let's put this down. What was the plan here, buddy?
我反應過度了 這一點都不鋒利
I overreacted. It's not even sharp.
腎上腺激素分泌過度
Adrenaline.
是不是只是擦傷 還是
Did it just graze me, or...?
不是 你被子彈正中胸膛
No, you got hit right in the square of the fucking chest.
- 到身體裡去了 - 你會沒事的
- Went straight through. - You're gonna be fine.
我不知道 流了好多血
No, I don't know about that. That's a lot of blood.
- 不要聽他說的 你會挺過去的 - 該死
- Don't listen to him. You're gonna make it. - Fuck.
嘿 如果你還想要希望 聽他的吧
Hey, if you want hope, listen to him.
如果你要聽真相
If you want the truth,
我是你的伙伴 對嗎 這是個壞消息
I'm your fucking guy, all right? This is bad news.
能不能幫幫我們
Can we get some help here?
別擔心 我們會讓你沒事的
Don't worry. We're gonna get you fixed up.
- 噢 我的耶穌啊 - 不好嗎 不好嗎
- Oh, Jesus Christ. - Is it bad? Is it bad?
- 這他媽是個大洞 - 是的
- That's a big fucking hole. - Yeah.
- 我就要死在這了 - 如果你要走 就走吧
- I'm gonna go to this light right here. - If you've gotta go, you gotta go.
請別讓我在他說話中死去
Please don't let me die with him talking.
我會照顧史黛西和你的孩子們
I'll take care of Stacy and your boys.
沒有比這更煩的了
That couldn't be more annoying.
我已經在努力不那麼煩了
I'm not trying to be annoying.
- 我在儘量弄得又去 - 那很煩人
- I'm trying to have fun. - It's annoying.
- 但是有用了 看看 - 看看誰在說話 你還好嗎
- It worked though. Look at that. - Look who's talking. You okay?
你在生死邊緣徘徊 現在又說話了真好
You've been drifting in and out. Nice to hear you talking.
- 那麼 醫生怎麼說的 我會死嗎
So, what do the doctors say? Am I gonna die?
- 是的 - 什麼
- Yes. - Yes?
- 不會 - 我們都會死的
- No. - We're all gonna die.
這很危險的 但是你沒事了
It's been touch-and-go, but you're gonna be fine.
醫生會讓你出院的
Doctors are gonna let you out.
- 很好 - 他們的確給了你鳥的心臟
- That's good. - They did have to give you a bird's heart.
- 天啊 - 你還適應嗎
- Oh, God. - You okay with that?
- 沒有 - 他在開玩笑
- No. - He's kidding.
我們在開玩笑
We're kidding.
那個心臟對我可能太老了
That heart would've been too old for me.
我昏迷了多久
How long was I out?
- 兩年 - 真的嗎
- Two years. - Really?
- 四天 - 那好多了
- Four days. - That's better.
你為什麼不玩了 反正我們已經說了兩年
Why didn't you play? Thought we were gonna say two years.
我們現在有了女總統
We've got a woman president.
該死
Shit.
- 看看誰來了 - 我的天啊 他在說話
- Look who's here. - Oh, my gosh. He's talking.
- 嗨 你在說話 - 我們不打擾你們了
- You're talking. Hi. - We'll leave you alone.
拜託 讓我來給你解釋一切
Please. Let me explain everything to you,
裡面有太多誤會了
there are so many misunderstandings.
- 沒事 朱莉亞解釋了一切 - 不要跟她說話 她瘋了
- It's okay. Julia explained everything. - Don't talk to her. She's crazy.
她告訴了我由於她的苦難把你捲入了這一切
She told me everything she put you through because of her affliction.
"她的苦難"
"Her affliction"?
她當時有心臟病
It's heartbreaking what she's been through.
- 嗨 - 她還跟我說了我丈夫
- Hi. - She also told me that my husband...
是唯一抵制她的誘惑的人
is the only one that ever resisted her.
- 好吧 - 黛爾 你真是個幸運的男人
- Okay. - Dale, you are one lucky man.
你太太真是善解人意 體貼入微
Your wife is so understanding and caring.
- 是的 - 還那麼漂亮
- Right. - So beautiful.
他非常樂意幫助我照顧寶寶 而且很有用
She has been so supportive with the babies. And helpful.
噢 拜託 這是我唯一能作為賠罪的
Oh. Please, it's the least I can do to make amends for my bad behavior.
好吧
Okay.
我會找到麥克醫生 告訴他能說話了
I'm gonna find Dr. Mike, tell him you're talking.
好的 很好 去找醫生 因為我感覺有點
Okay, good. Go get the doctor because I'm feeling a little...
你來這裡幹什麼
What is going on here?
怎麼了 我擺脫你了 沒有什麼大白鯨交易 或者其他的
What's up? I'm off the hook? No more white-whale business? Or any of that?
- 沒有了 你已經擺脫我了 - 真的嗎
- No more. You're off the hook. - Really?
你知道男人在昏迷中仍然可以勃起嗎
Did you know that when men are in a coma they can still get an erection?
真的哦 黛爾 昏迷勃起者
It's true, Dale. Coma boners.
"昏迷勃起者" 什麼啊
"Coma boner"? What?
昏迷中勃起很多很多次
Lots and lots of coma boners.
想想吧
Think about it.
- 該死 - 好吧 好吧 我還是走吧
- Oh, shit. - All right, well, I better go.
我為我和史黛西預約了溫泉理療
I'm booking a spa day for me and Stacy.
- 我會幹你的老婆 黛爾 - 不要 不要
- I'm gonna fuck your wife, Dale. - No, no.
不要 不要 等一下 不要
No. No, you're not. Hang on. Hang on. No.
- 嘿 他在這 - 孩子們
- Hey, there she is. - Boys.
你看起來真美 你知道
You look fantastic. You know,
我給你發了很多簡訊都沒有收到回復
I've been sending you a lot of unanswered texts.
你不是這麼吸引他們的
That's not how you catch them.
我覺得她要去幹我老婆
I think she said she's gonna fuck my wife.
- 其實她已經幹了 - 如脫韁的馬無法挽回了
- Thought she already did. - That horse may have left the barn.
我感覺她們倆已經基情四射了
I figured those guys have been bumping tacos.
她們最近非常親密
Super touchy-feely lately.
我不能讓它發生 太過分了
I can't process this. This is too much.
那麼 最後怎麼樣了
Anyway, so, what's even going on?
我們有沒有跟警察搞出什麼麻煩
Did we get in trouble with the police, or...?
有麻煩
We did, yeah.
- 是的 很多麻煩 - 我們因為一長串重罪被捕
- Yeah. A lot. - We got arrested for a long list of felonies.
但是因為你替探長挨了槍
But because you took a bullet for the detective,
地方檢察官給我們赦免了很多
DA got rid of the biggies.
減免費用了嗎 很好
Dropped some charges? Nice.
凱文·科斯特納:美國著名演員 導演 奧斯卡最佳導演及影片等七項大獎
我覺得你有點像凱文·科斯特納
You're like a little Kevin Costner.
你是我們的守衛者
You're our bodyguard.
說的好聽 好吧 看來我們保住了我們的生意
Pretty sweet. All right, so I'm guessing we saved the business.
- 沒有 - 沒保住
- Nope. We did not. - We did not.
幾天前銀行取消了抵押品贖回權
The bank foreclosed a couple days ago.
一次 兩次 成交 D.H商業信託競拍成功
Going once, going twice, sold. To D.H. Commercial Trust.
但也有個好消息
But there's good news.
買我們公司的人讓我們繼續運營
The guy who bought the company is keeping us on to run it.
如果我們減到三百塊 你就有
If we bring that down to $300, you've got...
盧佩 好吧
Lupe. All right.
你好 盧佩
Hola, Lupe.
- 空中商城 - 是的 空中商城
- SkyMall? - Sí, SkyMall.
很好 是個好消息
Great. That's great news.
- 空中商城的訂貨已經裝載到船上了 - 老闆會愛死這個的
- SkyMall order is ready to ship. - The boss is gonna love that.
是的 我們去給他看看這個大數字吧
Yes. Let's go show him these great numbers too.
我們應該為這些數字高興嗎
Are we happy with these numbers?
這很不錯的
They're pretty good.
- 還有提高的空間 - 我們還能做得更好
- Room for improvement. - We can do better.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我剛剛明白
I just realized.
你們以為你們給我帶來了好消息
You actually thought you were bringing me good news.
你們三個走進來 帶著可悲的微笑
The three of you walked in with smiles on your fucking pathetic faces.
你們為什麼會存在 你們三個為什麼要存在
Why were you born? Why were the three of you born?
看著你們就像看著愚蠢無能的大峽谷
Looking at you is like looking out over the Grand Canyon of ineptitude.
你們父母沒把你們掐死真是奇蹟
It's a wonder your parents didn't smother you...
- 你們要去哪 - 下週見
- Where you going? - See you next week.
我有個主意 你們為什麼不嘗試自殺協議
I have an idea. Why don't you try a suicide pact?
我沒說把你們扔下大樓或者吃點安眠藥
And I'm not talking about throwing yourself off a building or some sleeping-pills shit.
我在說 你們幾個就應該自相殘殺
I'm talking about, you fuck each other to death.
你們他媽的要去哪 我真是欠你們的
Where the fuck do you think you're going? I own you!
老闆不是人2
好吧
Well,
我們在你的地區有經營權自由的機會
we have several franchise opportunities available in your area.
但是買店需要
But, purchasing a store requires...
一項重要的首期付款
a significant up-front investment.
好吧 這種情況的話
Well, in that case...
先給我去掉三個地區
start me off with three locations.
我確定我們可以讓你滿意 瓊斯先生
I'm sure that we can accommodate you, Mr. Jones.
拜託 瓊斯先生 那是我爸爸
Please. Mr. Jones? That's my daddy.
叫我混蛋
Call me Motherfucker.
每次 這傢伙
Every... This guy.
好吧 首先我們要把雷克斯
Okay. First we tie up Rex in one of
在第三大街的某個廢棄倉庫裡綁起來
those abandoned warehouses off 3rd.
首先我們要把雷克斯...
First we're gonna tie up Rex...
首先我們要把雷克斯... 哇靠
First we're gonna tie up Rex... Fuck off, everyone.
伯特的車一到達地下後 警察就會失去...
As soon as Bert's car is underground, the police lose...
伯特的車到達地下 是嗎
Bert's car goes underground, right?
警察就會失去追蹤信號
Police lose the signal from the wire.
你們有公司停車位嗎
Do you guys validate parking?
我不是說你 很明顯 那會是種族歧視
Not you personally, obviously, that'd be racist.
你們要把車停到4421位
You're gonna pull into Space 4421...
我會回電給你
I gotta call you back.
銀行兩天前取消了抵押品的贖回權
The bank foreclosed two days ago.
- 嘿 但這有個好消息 - 真的嗎
- Hey, but there is good news. - Really?
"真的嗎"
"Really?"
我們需要跟一些合法的人談談
We need to talk to somebody legitimate.
我們需要一些能讓我們公司起死回生的人
We need to find someone who can get us our company back.
我不能帶你去下一個場景 我不能
I can't take you to the next scene any better than that. I can't.
好吧 然後我會和丹尼爾·克雷格[銀屏猛男]成親
Well, then I would marry Daniel Craig...
我要上了肖恩·康納利[演員] 再殺了提摩西·道爾頓[演員]
I'd fuck Sean Connery and kill Timothy Dalton.
我會娶愛德·赫爾姆斯
I would marry Ed Helms,
上了布萊德利·庫伯[演員]
fuck Bradley Cooper
再殺了扎克·加利費安納基斯
and kill Zach Galifianakis.
娶了龜裂 上了愛德 殺了庫伯 對嗎
Marry Crackle, fuck Snap, kill Pop. Right?
我的天啊 你這到這像什麼嗎
Oh, my God. Do you know what this looks like?
什麼
What?
像我們不知道我們在幹什麼
It looks like we don't know what we're doing.
伙伴 你不要叫我的名字我會很喜歡的
Boy, I'd love it if you'd stop saying my name.
等一下 嘿 站住
Hang on a second. Hey, freeze.
猜猜誰手上有槍
Guess who's got the gun now.
我
Me.
你覺得她從哪學來的
Where do you think she learned it?
也許是第一部
Maybe from the first movie.
椅子準備好了 我要去小便一下
Get that chair ready. I'm gonna take a tinkle.
噢 但是我很饑渴
Oh, but I'm thirsty.
在我身上哆嗦吧
Save me a shake.
我沒辦法說出來
I just can't say it.
所以你想用贖金
So you wanna use the ransom...
下面是什麼
What is it?
"你打算用贖金來拯救你的生意"
"Y'all plan to use the ransom to save y'all business."
我只是想聽你說
I just like to hear you say it.
拜託 伙伴
Come on, man.
幫幫我 也幫幫你們 像我那死老爹身上復仇吧
Help me help you get revenge on my asshole...
- 我的死... - 死老爹
- My asshole... - Asshole dad.
你必須去拿到這裡面屬於你的 這裡
You have to take what's yours in this... In this...
- 我指 你必須去 - 你必須去
- I mean, you have to... - You have to...
- ...去拿屬於你生命裡的 - 拿去吧
- ...take what's yours in this life. - Take it.
抓緊他
Grab it!
你們那空虛萎縮的蛋蛋馬上就完了
You will pass your empty, sac-less ball sacs...
不對 是...
No, that's...
"空虛枯萎的蛋蛋" 他們是枯萎的
"Empty shriveled sacs." They're shriveled.
看著你們我知道那是多枯萎
I should know that just looking at you.
這是你欠我們的場景
That's your credit picture right there.
- 來了個大塊頭 - 我聞到狗屎味了
- Here comes the heavy. - I smell dog shit.
- 真的 - 是的
- Do you really? - Yeah.
也能是你裝的
It might be your acting.